<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/recent/</link>
		<title>Recent Announcements</title>
		<description>The AWS Cloud platform expands daily. Learn about announcements, launches, news, innovation and more from Amazon Web Services.</description>
		<managingEditor>aws@amazon.com (Amazon Web Services)</managingEditor>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:09:01 GMT</pubDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<image>
			<url>https://a0.awsstatic.com/main/images/logos/aws_logo_smile_179x109.png</url>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/recent/</link>
			<title>Recent Announcements</title>
			<description>The AWS Cloud platform expands daily. Learn about announcements, launches, news, innovation and more from Amazon Web Services.</description>
		</image>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">c85179db9711d1e2a7259b7b651268ca98406aaa</guid>
			<title>CloudWatch Database Insights adds support for RDS databases</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;CloudWatch Database Insights announces support of databases hosted on Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS). Database Insights is a database observability solution that provides a curated experience designed for DevOps engineers, application developers, and database administrators (DBAs) to expedite database troubleshooting and gain a holistic view into their database fleet health.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Database Insights consolidates logs and metrics from your applications, your databases, and the operating systems on which they run into a unified view in the console. Using its pre-built dashboards, recommended alarms, and automated telemetry collection, you can monitor the health of your database fleets and use a guided troubleshooting experience to drill down to individual instances for root-cause analysis. Application developers can correlate the impact of database dependencies with the performance and availability of their business-critical applications. This is because they can drill down from the context of their application performance view in Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals to the specific dependent database in Database Insights.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can get started with Database Insights by enabling it on your RDS databases using the RDS service console, AWS APIs, and SDKs. Database Insights delivers database health monitoring aggregated at the fleet level, as well as instance-level dashboards for detailed database and SQL query analysis.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Database Insights is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all public AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; and applies a new vCPU-based pricing – see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt; for details. For further information, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/Database-Insights.html" target="_blank"&gt;Database Insights documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/databases,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/cloudwatch-database-insights-rds-databases</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">0f903827d9fc8b0b89161a2180aab85d53f68a05</guid>
			<title>AWS WAF enhances integration with Service Quotas</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS WAF enhances Service Quotas capabilities, enabling organizations to proactively monitor and manage quotas for their cloud deployments.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS WAF is a web application firewall that helps protect your web applications or APIs against common web exploits and bots that may affect availability, compromise security, or consume excessive resources. By leveraging AWS Service Quotas, you can quickly understand your applied service quota values for these WAF resources and request increases when needed. This enhanced integration brings three key benefits. First, you can now monitor the current utilization of your account-level quotas for WAF resources such as web ACLs, rule groups, and IP sets in the Service Quotas console. Second, certain service quota increase requests will now be auto-approved, enabling customers to access higher quotas faster. For example, smaller increases are usually automatically approved while larger requests are submitted to AWS Support. Lastly, you can now create &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon CloudWatch&lt;/a&gt; alarms to notify you when your utilization of a given quota exceeds a configurable threshold. This enables you to better adapt your utilization based on your applied quota values and automate your quota increase requests.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can access &lt;a href="https://us-east-1.console.aws.amazon.com/servicequotas/home/services/s3/quotas" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Service Quotas&lt;/a&gt; through the AWS console, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/servicequotas/2019-06-24/apireference/Welcome.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS APIs&lt;/a&gt;, and CLI. Integration with AWS Service Quotas is available in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS regions&lt;/a&gt; where AWS WAF is offered. You can learn more about AWS WAF by visiting &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/waf-chapter.html" target="_blank"&gt;Developer Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-waf</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-waf-enhances-integration-service-quotas/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e7d6bfd9f9c272cfbd77eb9bdf41f5b00c7c7cb9</guid>
			<title>Amazon Verified Permissions now supports the Cedar JSON entity format</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Verified Permissions now supports the same JSON format for entity and context data, as the Cedar SDK. Developers can use this simpler format for authorization requests. This aligns the Amazon Verified Permissions API more closely with the open source Cedar SDK, and simplifies moving from the SDK to Amazon Verified Permissions or vice versa.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon Verified Permissions is a permissions management and fine-grained authorization service for the applications that you build. Using &lt;a href="https://www.cedarpolicy.com/en" target="_blank"&gt;Cedar&lt;/a&gt;, an expressive and analyzable open-source policy language, developers and admins can define policy-based access controls using roles and attributes for more granular, context-aware access control. For example, an HR application might call Amazon Verified Permissions (AVP) to determine if Alice is permitted to access Bob’s performance evaluation, given that she is in the HR Managers group. Customers can use Cedar JSON format to pass entity data describing the principal (Alice) and the resource (Bob’s performance evaluation).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This change is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all AWS regions&lt;/a&gt; supported by Amazon Verified Permissions. The service will continue to support the old format, and so the change does not break existing application integrations. To learn more about using the Cedar JSON format, see &lt;a href="https://docs.cedarpolicy.com/auth/entities-syntax.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cedar JSON entity &lt;/a&gt;in the Cedar user guide and the Verified Permissions user guide. To learn more about Amazon Verified Permissions, visit the product page. For more information visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/verified-permissions" target="_blank"&gt;Verified Permissions product page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-verified-permissions,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-verified-permissions-cedar-json-entity-format/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">9121d9ff99c13708eab720ef4478bf697a072a6d</guid>
			<title>Anthropic's Claude 3.7 Sonnet is now available in Amazon Bedrock</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropic's Claude 3.7 Sonnet hybrid reasoning model, their most intelligent model to date, is now available in Amazon Bedrock. Claude 3.7 Sonnet represents a significant advancement in AI capabilities, offering both quick responses and extended, step-by-step thinking made visible to the user. This new model includes strong improvements in coding and brings enhanced performance across various tasks, like instruction following, math, and physics.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Claude 3.7 Sonnet introduces a unique approach to AI reasoning by integrating it seamlessly with other capabilities. Unlike traditional models that separate quick responses from those requiring deeper thought, Claude 3.7 Sonnet allows users to toggle between &lt;em&gt;standard &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;extended thinking &lt;/em&gt;modes. In standard mode, it functions as an upgraded version of Claude 3.5 Sonnet. While in extended thinking mode, it employs self-reflection to achieve improved results across a wide range of tasks. Amazon Bedrock users can adjust how long the model thinks, offering a flexible trade-off between speed and answer quality. Additionally, users can control the reasoning budget by specifying a token limit, enabling more precise management of cost.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Anthropic has optimized Claude 3.7 Sonnet for real-world applications that align closely with typical language model use cases, rather than focusing solely on math and computer science competition problems. This approach ensures that the model is well-suited to address the diverse needs of customers across various industries and use cases.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Claude 3.7 Sonnet is now available in Amazon Bedrock in the US East (N. Virginia), US East (Ohio), and US West (Oregon) regions. To get started, visit the Amazon Bedrock &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/" target="_blank"&gt;console&lt;/a&gt;. Integrate it into your applications using the Amazon Bedrock API or SDK. For more information and to learn more read the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-7-sonnet-the-first-hybrid-reasoning-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock" target="_blank"&gt;AWS News Blog&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/claude/" target="_blank"&gt;Claude in Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; product detail page.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/anthropics-claude-3-7-sonnet-amazon-bedrock/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">018254161f4277dea1cd491159c9f1df074cbd85</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 C7gd instances are now available in the AWS GovCloud (US-East) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7gd instances with up to 3.8 TB of local NVMe-based SSD block-level storage are available in the AWS GovCloud (US-East) Region.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These Graviton3-based instances with DDR5 memory are built on the AWS Nitro System and are a great fit for applications that need access to high-speed, low latency local storage, including those that need temporary storage of data for scratch space, temporary files, and caches. They have up to 45% improved real-time NVMe storage performance than comparable Graviton2-based instances. Graviton3-based instances also use up to 60% less energy for the same performance than comparable EC2 instances, enabling you to reduce your carbon footprint in the cloud.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; C7gd instances are now available in the following AWS regions: US East (N. Virginia, Ohio), US West (Oregon, N. California), Europe (Spain, Stockholm, Ireland, Frankfurt), Asia Pacific (Tokyo, Mumbai, Singapore, Sydney, Malaysia) and AWS GovCloud (US-East).&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-ec2</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-c7gd-instances-govcloud-us-east-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">d124da9d46c82ffe484fed33ff86d7b941bf09ca</guid>
			<title>Certificate-Based Authentication is now available on Amazon AppStream 2.0 multi-session fleets</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon AppStream 2.0 improves the end-user experience by adding support for certificate-based authentication (CBA) on multi-session fleets running the Microsoft Windows operating system and joined to an Active Directory. This functionality helps administrators to leverage the cost benefits of the multi-session model while providing an enhanced end-user experience. By combining these enhancements with the existing advantages of multi-session fleets, AppStream 2.0 offers a solution that helps balance cost-efficiency and user satisfaction.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; By using certificate-based authentication, you can rely on the security and logon experience features of your SAML 2.0 identity provider, such as passwordless authentication, to access AppStream 2.0 resources. Certificate-based authentication with AppStream 2.0 enables a single sign-on logon experience to access domain-joined desktop and application streaming sessions without separate password prompts for Active Directory.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available at no additional cost in all the AWS &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;Regions&lt;/a&gt; where Amazon AppStream 2.0 is available. AppStream 2.0 offers pay-as-you go &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/appstream2/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing&lt;/a&gt;. To get started with AppStream 2.0, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/appstream2/getting-started/" target="_blank"&gt;Getting Started with Amazon AppStream 2.0&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To enable this feature for your users, you must use an AppStream 2.0 image that uses &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/appstream2/latest/developerguide/base-images-agent.html" target="_blank"&gt;AppStream 2.0 agent&lt;/a&gt; released on or after February 7, 2025&amp;nbsp;or your image is using &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/appstream2/latest/developerguide/administer-images.html#keep-image-updated-managed-image-updates" target="_blank"&gt;Managed AppStream 2.0 image updates&lt;/a&gt; released on or after February 11, 2025.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-appstream-2-0,marketing:marchitecture/desktop-and-app-streaming</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/certificate-based-authentication-amazon-appstream-2-0-multi-session-fleets</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">746312a5c0a98af01778e04eeb16ce8ff0c6ccb6</guid>
			<title>AWS CodePipeline adds native Amazon EC2 deployment support</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CodePipeline introduces a new action to deploy to Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2). This action enables you to easily deploy your application to a group of EC2 instances behind load balancers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Previously, if you wanted to deploy to EC2 instances, you had to use CodeDeploy with an AppSpec file to configure the deployment. Now, you can simply use this new EC2 deploy action in your pipeline to deploy to EC2 instances, without the necessity of managing CodeDeploy resources. This streamlined approach reduces your operational overhead and simplifies your deployment process.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about using the EC2 deploy action in your pipeline, visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/latest/userguide/tutorials-ec2-deploy.html" target="_blank"&gt;tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/latest/userguide/action-reference-EC2Deploy.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. For more information about AWS CodePipeline, visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;. This new action is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all regions &lt;/a&gt;where AWS CodePipeline is supported, except the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions and the China Regions.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,general:products/aws-codepipeline</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-codepipeline-native-ec2-deployment-support/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">67d4d80755fe288afe5f449b0e55a20652c02f2f</guid>
			<title>AWS Database Migration Service now supports Multi-ENI networking for homogeneous migrations.</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Database Migration Service (DMS) now supports the Multi-ENI networking model and Credentials Vending System for DMS Homogenous Migrations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers can now choose the Multi-ENI connection type and use the Credentials Vending System, providing a simplified networking configuration experience for secure connectivity to their on-premises database instances.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;For information see documentation for AWS &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/dms/latest/userguide/data-migrations.html" target="_blank"&gt;DMS Homogeneous Migrations&lt;/a&gt;. For AWS DMS regional availability, please refer to the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region Table&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-database-migration-service,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-database-migration-service-multi-eni-networking/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">4d19ee177286b62614f1d385d05c2f003aa3b0ea</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL supports minor versions 17.4, 16.8, 15.12, 14.17, 13.20</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/postgresql/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)&lt;/a&gt; for PostgreSQL now supports the latest minor versions 17.4, 16.8, 15.12, 14.17, and 13.20. Please note, this release supports the versions released by the PostgreSQL community on &lt;a href="https://www.postgresql.org/about/news/out-of-cycle-release-scheduled-for-february-20-2025-3016/" target="_blank"&gt;February, 20,2025 &lt;/a&gt;to address the regression that was part of the February 13, 2025 release. We recommend that you upgrade to the latest minor versions to fix known security vulnerabilities in prior versions of PostgreSQL, and to benefit from the bug fixes added by the PostgreSQL community.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can use automatic minor version upgrades to automatically upgrade your databases to more recent minor versions during scheduled maintenance windows. You can also use Amazon RDS Blue/Green deployments for RDS for PostgreSQL using&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;physical replication for your minor version upgrades. Learn more about upgrading your database instances, including automatic minor version upgrades and Blue/Green Deployments in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_UpgradeDBInstance.PostgreSQL.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL makes it simple to set up, operate, and scale PostgreSQL deployments in the cloud. See &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/postgresql/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL Pricing&lt;/a&gt; for pricing details and regional availability. Create or update a fully managed Amazon RDS database in the Amazon RDS Management Console.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-rds,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-postgresql-supports-minor-versions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">0606aa78e2f64ace4dba95d0a4e884e621f00a42</guid>
			<title>Amazon MSK adds support for Apache Kafka version 3.8</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/msk/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka&lt;/a&gt; (Amazon MSK) now supports Apache Kafka version 3.8. You can now create new clusters using version 3.8 with either KRAFT or ZooKeeper mode for metadata management or upgrade your existing ZooKeeper based clusters to use version 3.8. Apache Kafka version 3.8 includes several bug fixes and new features that improve performance. Key new features include support for compression level configuration. This allows you to further optimize your performance when using compression types such as lz4, zstd and gzip, by allowing you to change the default compression level. For more details and a complete list of improvements and bug fixes, see the &lt;a href="https://downloads.apache.org/kafka/3.8.0/RELEASE_NOTES.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apache Kafka release notes for version 3.8&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon MSK is a fully managed service for Apache Kafka and Kafka Connect that makes it easier for you to build and run applications that use Apache Kafka as a data store. Amazon MSK is compatible with Apache Kafka, which enables you to quickly migrate your existing Apache Kafka workloads to Amazon MSK with confidence or build new ones from scratch. With Amazon MSK, you can spend more time innovating on streaming applications and less time managing Apache Kafka clusters. To learn how to get started, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/msk/latest/developerguide/getting-started.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon MSK Developer Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Support for Apache Kafka version 3.8 is offered in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS regions&lt;/a&gt; where Amazon MSK is available.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-msk,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-msk-apache-kafka-version-3-8/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">872d5a570dfc4acf4e0c9bf5a1bcae49099a268f</guid>
			<title>Announcing fine-grained access control via AWS Lake Formation with EMR on EKS</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the general availability of fine-grained data access control (FGAC) via AWS Lake Formation for Apache Spark with Amazon EMR on EKS. This enables you to enforce full FGAC policies (database, table, column, row, and cell-level) defined in Lake Formation for your data lake tables from EMR on EKS Spark jobs. We are also sharing the general availability of Glue Data Catalog views with EMR on EKS for Spark workflows.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Lake Formation simplifies building, securing, and managing data lakes by allowing you to define fine-grained access controls through grant and revoke statements, similar to RDBMS. The same Lake Formation rules now apply to Spark jobs on EMR on EKS for Hudi, Delta Lake, and Iceberg table formats, further simplifying data lake security and governance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS Glue Data Catalog views with EMR on EKS allows customers to create views from Spark jobs that can be queried from multiple engines without requiring access to referenced tables. Administrators can control underlying data access using the rich SQL dialect provided by EMR on EKS Spark jobs. Access is managed with AWS Lake Formation permissions, including named resource grants, data filters, and lake formation tags. All requests are logged in AWS CloudTrail.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Fine-grained access control for Apache Spark batch jobs on EMR on EKS is available with the EMR 7.7 release in all regions where EMR on EKS is available. To get started, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/emr/latest/EMR-on-EKS-DevelopmentGuide/security_iam_fgac-lf.html" target="_blank"&gt;Using AWS Lake Formation with Amazon EMR on EKS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-lake-formation,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,general:products/amazon-emr,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/fine-grained-control-aws-lake-formation-emr-eks/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">52d613da87711e0a92c4e3a18704b140c28b17d6</guid>
			<title>You can now use your China UnionPay credit card to create an AWS account</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services, Inc. now supports China UnionPay credit cards for creating new AWS accounts, eliminating the need for international credit cards for customers in China.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To use China UnionPay for creating your AWS account, enter your address and billing country in China, then provide your local China UnionPay credit card details and verify your personal identity or business license. All subsequent AWS charges will be billed in Chinese Yuan currency, providing convenient payment experience for customers in China.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, select China UnionPay as your payment method when creating a new AWS account. For more information on using China UnionPay credit cards with AWS, visit &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/manage-payment-cny.html#yuan-cc-first-time" target="_blank"&gt;Set up a Chinese yuan credit card&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/cloud-financial-management,marketing:marchitecture/cost-management</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/china-unionpay-credit-card-create-aws-account/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">22042529db0c518cd2e64928fe3ec9d0b1e25d11</guid>
			<title>AWS CodePipeline adds native Amazon EKS deployment support</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CodePipeline introduces a new action to deploy to Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). This action enables you to easily deploy your container applications to your EKS clusters, including those in private VPCs.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Previously, if you wanted to deploy to a EKS cluster within a private network, you had to initialize and maintain a compute environment within the private network. Now, you can simply provide the name of the EKS cluster and add this action to your pipeline. The pipeline will automatically establish a connection into your private network to deploy your container application, without additional infrastructure needed. This streamlined approach reduces your operational overhead and simplifies your deployment process.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about using the EKS action in your pipeline, visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/latest/userguide/tutorials-eks-deploy.html" target="_blank"&gt;tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/latest/userguide/action-reference-EKS.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. For more information about AWS CodePipeline, visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;. This new action is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all regions &lt;/a&gt;where AWS CodePipeline is supported, except the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions and the China Regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-codepipeline,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-codepipeline-native-amazon-eks-deployment-support</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6f6e039d62c822297fe6eee1f840f3ce9f253bf8</guid>
			<title>Amazon Bedrock now available in Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) and Asia Pacific (Osaka) regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Beginning today, customers can use Amazon Bedrock in the Asia Pacific (Hyderabad) and Asia Pacific (Osaka) regions to easily build and scale generative AI applications using a variety of foundation models (FMs) as well as powerful tools to build generative AI applications.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon Bedrock is a fully managed service that offers a choice of high-performing large language models (LLMs) and other FMs from leading AI companies via a single API. Amazon Bedrock also provides a broad set of capabilities customers need to build generative AI applications with security, privacy, and responsible AI built in. These capabilities help you build tailored applications for multiple use cases across different industries, helping organizations unlock sustained growth from generative AI while ensuring customer trust and data governance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Bedrock page&lt;/a&gt; and see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Bedrock documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-bedrock</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-bedrock-hyderabad-osaka-regions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">53b1d8ddf16cb2e61cf1a42cc6a3645261f70ef4</guid>
			<title>Amazon Elastic Beanstalk now supports Windows Server 2025 and Windows Server Core 2025 environments</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Elastic Beanstalk now enables customers to deploy applications on Windows Server 2025 and Windows Server Core 2025 environments. These environments come pre-configured with .NET Framework 4.8.1 and .NET 8.0, providing developers with the latest Long Term Support (LTS) version of .NET alongside the established .NET Framework&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Windows Server 2025 and Windows Server Core 2025 delivers enhanced security features and performance improvements. Developers can create Elastic Beanstalk environments on Windows Server 2025 using the Elastic Beanstalk Console, CLI, API, or AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This platform is generally available in commercial regions where Elastic Beanstalk is available including the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. For a complete list of regions and service offerings, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;For more information about .NET on Windows Server platforms, see the Elastic Beanstalk &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/latest/dg/create_deploy_NET.html" target="_blank"&gt;developer guide&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more about Elastic Beanstalk, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/" target="_blank"&gt;Elastic Beanstalk product page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-elastic-beanstalk,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-elastic-beanstalk-windows-server-2025-core-environments/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">7381fab5bf9a84b3c27b2099275fbd93cfe3bfad</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 G6e instances now available in Stockholm region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, the Amazon EC2 G6e instances powered by NVIDIA L40S Tensor Core GPUs is now available in Europe (Stockholm) region. G6e instances can be used for a wide range of machine learning and spatial computing use cases.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers can use G6e instances to deploy large language models (LLMs) with up to 13B parameters and diffusion models for generating images, video, and audio. Additionally, the G6e instances will unlock customers’ ability to create larger, more immersive 3D simulations and digital twins for spatial computing workloads. G6e instances feature up to 8 NVIDIA L40S Tensor Core GPUs with 48 GB of memory per GPU and third generation AMD EPYC processors. They also support up to 192 vCPUs, up to 400 Gbps of network bandwidth, up to 1.536 TB of system memory, and up to 7.6 TB of local NVMe SSD storage. Developers can run AI inference workloads on G6e instances using AWS Deep Learning AMIs, AWS Deep Learning Containers, or managed services such as Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS), AWS Batch, and Amazon SageMaker.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EC2 G6e instances are available today in the AWS US East (N. Virginia, Ohio), US West (Oregon), Asia Pacific (Tokyo), and Europe (Frankfurt, Spain, Stockholm) regions. Customers can purchase G6e instances as On-Demand Instances, Reserved Instances, Spot Instances, or as part of Savings Plans.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, visit the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cli/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Command Line Interface&lt;/a&gt; (CLI), and AWS SDKs. To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/g6e/" target="_blank"&gt;G6e instance page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-g6e-instances-stockholm-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e5deb16543e8c9205f4916a52f99c0ce5c41b7e1</guid>
			<title>AWS announces Backup Payment Methods for invoices</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the introduction of Backup Payment Methods for AWS invoices in all commercial AWS Regions. This feature enables customers to set up alternate payment methods that will be automatically charged for their invoices if the primary payment method fails. This will help customers make timely invoice payments without the need for manual intervention or last-minute payment updates.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; There are several benefits this feature brings to AWS customers. Firstly, it reduces the risk of missed or late payments due to issues with the primary payment method. Backup payment method provides peace of mind, knowing that there's a fallback payment method in place for invoice payments, reducing the risk of failed invoice payments. This can help maintain uninterrupted access to AWS services and avoid potential service disruptions. Secondly, it saves time and effort for customers by eliminating the need to manually update payment details or coordinate with their finance and accounting teams to settle invoices when the primary method fails.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started with Backup Payment Methods, customers can access their AWS Console and navigate to the billing section. From there, they can set their preferences for backup payment methods at any time. For more information on how to set up and manage Backup Payment Methods, please visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/manage-backuppaymentmethod.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Billing and Cost Management documentation page&lt;/a&gt; or contact your AWS account representative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-account-billing,marketing:marchitecture/cost-management</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-backup-payment-methods-invoices/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">13a431ac9afffb1a6e0f887d429db7d7ce6e5471</guid>
			<title>SES Outbound now delivers to Mail Manager Archives</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Simple Email Service (SES) announces that Outbound customers can now specify a Mail Manager archive resource as an additional destination for outbound mail workloads. This enables retention of messages post-DKIM-signature, ensuring that the archive is usable for validating every individual sent message. The Mail Manager archive search interface allows easy discovery of indexed messages and presents search results directly in the AWS console, or makes them available to export to the customer’s chosen S3 bucket.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; SES Outbound customers using APIv2 now have access to a new parameter in their configuration set which specifies a Mail Manager archive ARN in the same . Once the necessary role permissions in IAM are configured, the user initiating the Outbound workload will see a copy of each uniquely-signed outgoing message ingested into the destination archive, where it will be indexed and made available for both search and export.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This new feature is billed at the existing Mail Manager Archive price points. This capability is available for Outbound customers in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/01/ses-mail-manager-available-new-regions/" target="_blank"&gt;all 17 AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where Mail Manager is launched. Customers can learn more about SES Outbound and Mail Manager &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ses/details/" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ses,marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/ses-outbound-delivers-mail-manager-archives</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6244f82e271cd461d777d5f89d5a7af9b935bf99</guid>
			<title>AWS Network Firewall introduces automated domain lists and insights</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/network-firewall/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Network Firewall&lt;/a&gt; now offers automated domain lists and insights, a feature that enhances visibility into network traffic and simplifies firewall rule configuration. This new capability analyzes HTTP and HTTPS traffic logs from the last 30 days and provides insights into frequently accessed domains, enabling quick rule creation based on observed network traffic patterns.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Many organizations now use allow-list policies to limit access to approved destinations only. Automated domain lists reduce the time and effort required to identify necessary domains, configure initial rules, and update allow lists as business needs change. This feature helps quickly identify legitimate traffic while maintaining a restrictive default stance, balancing security with operational efficiency.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is supported in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where AWS Network Firewall is available today. There is no additional cost to generate automated domain lists and insights on AWS Network Firewall.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, visit the AWS Network Firewall console and enable analysis mode for your firewall. For more information, please refer to the AWS Network Firewall service &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/network-firewall/latest/developerguide/firewall-creating.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 21:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-network-firewall,marketing:marchitecture/networking,general:products/aws-transit-gateway,general:products/amazon-vpc</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-network-firewall-automated-domain-lists</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">865e703f295c1ec1e4b12a486a22e08482d1abf7</guid>
			<title>Amazon ECS increases the CPU limit for ECS tasks to 192 vCPUs </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) now supports CPU limits of up to 192 vCPU for ECS tasks deployed on Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances, an increase from the previous 10 vCPU limit. This enhancement allows customers to more effectively manage resource allocation on larger Amazon EC2 instances.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon ECS customers can define soft and hard limits for CPU and memory resources at the container level, and hard limits at the task level. Soft limits reserve resources on an Amazon EC2 instance for a container, while hard limits enforce maximum usage. For CPU specifically, the container-level hard limit acts as a ceiling and helps prevent resource contention when multiple containers are competing for resources using Linux CpuShares. The task-level CPU limit acts both as the reservation for the task and prevents any single task from consuming excessive resources during contentions. Customers can now specify up to 192 vCPU as the CPU limit for an ECS task, increased from the previous 10 vCPU, enabling more effective resource sharing across multiple tasks on larger sized EC2 instances. For example, on a c7i.48xl instance with 192 vCPUs, defining a 32 vCPU limit per ECS task allows running up to 6 tasks without resource contention from noisy neighbors.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can use AWS management console, SDK, CLI, CloudFormation, or CDK to define the CPU limit for your Amazon ECS task definition. The new limit is now effective in all regions. To learn more, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonECS/latest/developerguide/task_definition_parameters.html#task_size" target="_blank"&gt;documentation. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/amazon-ecs</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ecs-increases-cpu-ecs-tasks/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">08dbb6b43be0d63025d8d317abc0f4fcfcbbf293</guid>
			<title>Announcing AWS DMS Serverless comprehensive premigration assessments</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/dms/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Database Migration Service Serverless&lt;/a&gt; (AWS DMS Serverless) now supports premigration assessments for replications . A premigration assessment evaluates the source and target databases of a database migration task to help identify problems that might prevent a migration from running as expected. By identifying and fixing these issues before a migration starts, you can avoid delays in completing the database migration.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The premigration assessments will obtain detailed information about the source schema and tables to provide recommendations on the AWS DMS settings that should be used. For example, the assessment can suggest which method of reading redo logs for change data capture (CDC) should be used or it could check if the recommended settings have been enabled, providing best practice recommendations from AWS DMS experts.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/dms/latest/userguide/CHAP_Tasks.AssessmentReport.html" target="_blank"&gt;Enabling and working with premigration assessments&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS DMS Serverless premigration assessments are available in all AWS Regions where DMS Serverless is available. For AWS DMS Serverless regional availability, please refer to the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region Table&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-database-migration-service,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-redshift</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-dms-serverless-comprehensive-premigration-assessments</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">34cb2f1d5245fccaf1a5a644c9f8741ca3644a6e</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for MySQL supports new minor versions 8.0.41 and 8.4.4</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/mysql/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for MySQL&lt;/a&gt; now supports MySQL minor versions 8.0.41 and 8.4.4. We recommend that you upgrade to the latest minor versions to fix known security vulnerabilities in prior versions of MySQL, and to benefit from the bug fixes, performance improvements, and new functionality added by the MySQL community. Learn more about the enhancements in RDS for MySQL 8.0.41 and 8.4.4 in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/MySQL.Concepts.VersionMgmt.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS user guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can leverage automatic minor version upgrades to automatically upgrade your databases to more recent minor versions during scheduled maintenance windows. You can also leverage &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/blue-green-deployments.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Managed Blue/Green deployments&lt;/a&gt; for safer, simpler, and faster updates to your MySQL instances. Learn more about upgrading your database instances, including automatic minor version upgrades and Blue/Green Deployments, in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_UpgradeDBInstance.MySQL.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS for MySQL makes it simple to set up, operate, and scale MySQL deployments in the cloud. Learn more about pricing details and regional availability at &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/mysql/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for MySQL&lt;/a&gt;. Create or update a fully managed Amazon RDS for MySQL database in the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/rds/home" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-rds-for-mysql,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-rds</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-mysql-new-minor-versions-8-0-41-8-4-4</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2ee2555d5a89b5f9da6b5a29a9ffe543a8dbf659</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 R6a instances now available in Canada (Central)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, the memory-optimized Amazon EC2 R6a instances are now available in Canada (Central) region. R6a instances are powered by third-generation AMD EPYC processors, and deliver up to 35% better price performance than comparable R5a instances. These instances offer 10% lower cost than comparable x86-based EC2 instances.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this additional region, R6a instances are available in the following AWS Regions: US East (Northern Virginia, Ohio), US West (Oregon, N. California), Asia Pacific (Mumbai, Hyderabad, Singapore, Sydney, Tokyo), Canada (Central), and Europe (Frankfurt, Ireland). These instances can be purchased as Savings Plans, Reserved, On-Demand, and Spot instances. To get started, visit the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cli/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Command Line Interface (CLI)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSJavaScriptSDK/latest/AWS/EC2.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS SDKs&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/r6a/" target="_blank"&gt;R6a instances&lt;/a&gt; pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-r6a-instances-canada-central</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2824d919eb63c1d5c6c4a1fa0a5cd4684f0ae0f3</guid>
			<title>AWS WAF enhances Data Protection and logging experience</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS WAF expands its &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/waf-data-protection-and-logging.html" target="_blank"&gt;Data Protection&lt;/a&gt; capabilities with new controls for sensitive data in logs. In addition, we have updated the Logging configuration console experience, making it easier for customer to select the optimal logging option.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Data Protection works together with existing &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/logging-management.html" target="_blank"&gt;Logging Redaction and Filtering&lt;/a&gt; features. You can select which protection method to use based on your use case and where you need to apply the controls. When configured, selected request log fields can be replaced with cryptographic hashes (e.g. ‘ade099751d2ea9f3393f0f’) or a predefined static string (‘REDACTED’) before logs are sent to WAF Sample Logs, Amazon Security Lake, CloudWatch, or other logging destinations. This centralized approach is designed to simplify the management of data and reduces the risk of accidental exposure. In addition, we simplified the WAF console experience for managing logging configurations. Customers can now view all available logging options and select their preferred settings in a simple unified experience.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all AWS Regions and endpoints where AWS WAF is available. To learn more, see the AWS WAF &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/waf-chapter.html" target="_blank"&gt;developer guide&lt;/a&gt;. There is no additional cost for using this feature, however standard AWS WAF charges still apply. For details, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/waf/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS WAF Pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To use the new Data Protection feature, simply navigate to your Web ACL 'Logging and metrics' section in the AWS WAF console and choose the desired data protection option. Existing logging configurations will remain unchanged. For more information about the Data Protection, visit &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/data-protection.html"&gt;AWS documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-waf,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-shield,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-waf-data-protection-logging-experience</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">45b733c3baea542b20e07b0b13f35087413b8885</guid>
			<title>AWS Storage Gateway is now available in AWS Mexico (Central) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/storagegateway/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Storage Gateway&lt;/a&gt; expands availability to the AWS Mexico (Central) Region enabling customers to deploy and manage hybrid cloud storage for their on-premises workloads.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS Storage Gateway is a hybrid cloud storage service that provides on-premises applications access to virtually unlimited storage in the cloud. You can use AWS Storage Gateway for backing up and archiving data to AWS, providing on-premises file shares backed by cloud storage, and providing on-premises applications low latency access to data in the cloud.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Visit the AWS Storage Gateway &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/storagegateway/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt; to learn more. Access the AWS Storage Gateway &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/storagegateway/" target="_blank"&gt;console&lt;/a&gt; to get started. To see all the Regions where AWS Storage Gateway is available, please visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region table&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/aws-storage-gateway</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-storage-gateway-mexico-central-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">d635ae9babaee2a8214ce95c28b73dd4b1c96178</guid>
			<title>Amazon Timestream for InfluxDB Adds Read Replica support</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Timestream for InfluxDB now supports Read Replicas, enabling customers to scale their read operations across multiple instances and Availability Zones. Customers can activate a Read Replica via the AWS Marketplace from the Timestream AWS Management Console while creating a Timestream for InfluxDB instance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Adding Read Replicas allow customers to support higher read throughput by distributing read requests across multiple database instances while maintaining a single write endpoint. This helps customers meet the demands of read-intensive workloads, such as real-time analytics and monitoring applications, and improve application performance and availability. Customers can create a Multi-AZ Read Replica cluster with just a few clicks in the AWS Management Console.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Support for Timestream for InfluxDB Read Replicas is available the following Timestream for InfluxDB Regions: US East (Ohio), US East (N. Virginia), US West (Oregon), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Asia Pacific (Singapore), Asia Pacific (Sydney), Asia Pacific (Tokyo), Canada (Central), Europe (Frankfurt), Europe (Ireland), Europe (London), Europe (Milan), Europe (Paris), and Europe (Stockholm). To learn more about Amazon Timestream for InfluxDB, please refer to our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/timestream/latest/developerguide/timestream-for-influxdb.html" target="_blank"&gt;user guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can create a Amazon Timestream for InfluxDB Read Replicas cluster from the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/timestream" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Timestream console&lt;/a&gt;, AWS Command line Interface (CLI), or SDK, and AWS CloudFormation. To learn more about the Read Replica Cluster for Amazon Timestream for InfluxDB, visit the&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/timestream/" target="_blank"&gt; product page,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/timestream/latest/developerguide/timestream-for-influxdb.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/timestream/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-timestream,marketing:marchitecture/aws-marketplace-and-partners</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-timestream-influxdb-read-replica-support/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">c4d3a3484d5f75b56449d0ab09ea5f54c8319a01</guid>
			<title>Amplify Hosting announces support for IAM roles for server-side rendered (SSR) applications </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;We're excited to announce the launch of IAM compute roles for AWS Amplify Hosting, enabling secure connections to other AWS resources from server-side rendered applications. This allows developers to integrate their SSR applications with AWS services while maintaining robust security practices.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Use Cases Unlocked:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Secure credential management for SSR applications&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Direct integration with AWS services like Secrets Manager and Parameter Store&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Support for database connections (RDS, DynamoDB)&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Granular permission controls&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;Branch-specific role configurations&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;This feature is available in all 20 AWS Amplify Hosting regions: US East (Ohio), US East (N. Virginia), US West (N. California), US West (Oregon), Asia Pacific (Hong Kong), Asia Pacific (Tokyo), Asia Pacific (Osaka) Asia Pacific (Seoul), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Asia Pacific (Singapore), Asia Pacific (Sydney), Canada (Central), Europe (Frankfurt), Europe (Stockholm), Europe (Milan), Europe (Ireland), Europe (London), Europe (Paris), Middle East (Bahrain) and South America (São Paulo).&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amplify/latest/userguide/amplify-SSR-compute-role.html" target="_blank"&gt;read the documentation&lt;/a&gt;. To get started with a tutorial, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/mobile/iam-compute-roles-for-server-side-rendering-with-aws-amplify-hosting/" target="_blank"&gt;check out our blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services,general:products/aws-amplify</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amplify-hosting-iam-roles-ssr-applications/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e59f084f089e1643a9c4d039b47ae8cdcde93418</guid>
			<title>Dynamically update your running EMR cluster with reconfiguration for instance fleets</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon EMR on EC2 now supports real-time update of application configurations for EMR instance fleets without requiring cluster termination or restart. With this feature, customers can now dynamically adjust application configurations, such as Spark’s executor memory, YARN’s resource allocation, and HDFS settings seamlessly, on a running cluster, minimizing interruptions to your workloads. This is particularly useful for adjusting resource allocation and fine-tune applications to match data processing and job performance requirements, while ensuring optimal resource utilization.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EMR is a cloud big data platform for data processing, interactive analysis, and machine learning using open-source frameworks such as &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/emr/features/spark/" target="_blank"&gt;Apache Spark&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/emr/latest/ReleaseGuide/emr-flink.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apache Flink&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/emr/latest/ReleaseGuide/emr-presto.html" target="_blank"&gt;Trino&lt;/a&gt;. Previously, you had to terminate and relaunch instance fleet clusters with new configurations. This process resulted in downtime, increased operational effort, and delayed workflow adjustments. With support for reconfiguration, EMR dynamically applies the updated configurations on cluster nodes on a rolling basis while ensuring cluster stability and resource availability. It provides notifications to customers via Amazon CloudWatch and EMR events. In the event of a failure or an incompatible update, EMR rolls back the changes to ensure your cluster remains operational. You can continue to run workloads on the cluster during the update process.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can leverage this feature on all EMR 5.21&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and later releases using AWS CLI, or API. This capability is available in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt;, including the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/govcloud-us/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS GovCloud (US) Regions&lt;/a&gt;, where Amazon EMR on EC2 is available. To learn more, please refer to the documentation &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/emr/latest/ManagementGuide/instance-fleet-reconfiguration.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/analytics,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-emr</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/update-running-emr-cluster-reconfiguration-instance-fleets</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6521dbdb1bc326cd2f334bcc70d6319ada76055a</guid>
			<title>AWS CDK releases L2 construct support for Amazon Data Firehose delivery streams</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) now includes L2 construct support for Amazon Data Firehose delivery streams, enabling developers to define and deploy streaming data infrastructure as code.&amp;nbsp;This new capability allows you to programmatically configure delivery streams that automatically deliver real-time data to destinations like Amazon S3.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this addition to AWS CDK, you can define sophisticated streaming architectures using familiar programming languages like TypeScript, Python, Java, and .NET. The module simplifies the process of setting up fully-managed delivery streams that push data to your desired destinations on a regular cadence, making it easier to build data lakes, enable real-time analytics, and create data archival solutions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about using Amazon Data Firehose with AWS CDK, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cdk/api/v2/docs/aws-cdk-lib.aws_kinesisfirehose-readme.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS CDK documentation&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/firehose/latest/dev/what-is-this-service.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Data Firehose Developer Guide&lt;/a&gt;. You can also explore sample applications and use cases on the AWS CDK Workshop website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,general:products/aws-cloud-development-kit</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-cdk-l2-construct-data-firehose-delivery-streams/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f5e726bde17f533259009e14d75b12261f4e6e2d</guid>
			<title>Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift now available in 18 additional regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL-Compatible Edition zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift is now supported in 18 additional regions, enabling near real-time analytics and machine learning (ML) using Amazon Redshift. With this launch, Aurora PostgreSQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift is supported in all AWS commercial regions where Amazon Redshift is supported.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift enables near real-time analytics and machine learning (ML) using Amazon Redshift to analyze petabytes of transactional data from Aurora. Within seconds of transactional data being written into Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL-Compatible Edition, zero-ETL seamlessly makes the data available in Amazon Redshift, removing the need to build and manage complex data pipelines that perform extract, transform, and load (ETL) operations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift is available for Aurora PostgreSQL version 16.4 and higher in US West (N. California), Africa (Cape Town), Asia Pacific (Hyderabad), Asia Pacific (Jakarta), Asia Pacific (Melbourne), Asia Pacific (Osaka), Asia Pacific (Seoul), Canada (Central), Canada West (Calgary), Europe (London), Europe (Milan), Europe (Paris), Europe (Spain), Europe (Zurich), Israel (Tel Aviv), Middle East (Bahrain), Middle East (UAE), South America (São Paulo). For all regions supported by the Aurora PostgreSQL zero-ETL integration, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/Concepts.Aurora_Fea_Regions_DB-eng.Feature.Zero-ETL.html" target="_blank"&gt;supported AWS regions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more and get started with zero-ETL integration, visit &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/zero-etl/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Aurora zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift&lt;/a&gt; and the getting started guides for &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/zero-etl.html" target="_blank"&gt;Aurora&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/zero-etl-using.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Redshift&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-aurora,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-redshift,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-aurora-postgresql-zero-etl-integration-redshift/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2c6f08a0be0fdde146b537230343e47b14c04739</guid>
			<title>AWS Price List API supports AWS PrivateLink</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Price List API now supports AWS PrivateLink. With AWS PrivateLink, you can simplify private network connectivity between virtual private clouds (VPCs), the AWS Price List API, and your on-premises data centers by using interface VPC endpoints and private IP addresses.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The AWS Price List API provides a catalog of the products and prices for AWS services that you can purchase on AWS.&lt;br&gt; AWS PrivateLink is compatible with AWS Direct Connect and AWS Virtual Private Network (VPN) to facilitate private network connectivity, and helps you eliminate the need to use public IP addresses, configure firewall rules, or configure an internet gateway to access the AWS Price List API from your on-premises data centers. Using the AWS Price List API with AWS Private Link enables you to access AWS product and pricing data without the need to access the public internet.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS PrivateLink for AWS Price List API is available in all commercial regions where the AWS Price List API is available (US East (N. Virginia), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Europe (Frankfurt), China (Ningxia). There is an additional cost to use this feature. Please see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/privatelink/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS PrivateLink pricing&lt;/a&gt; for more details.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can get started with the feature by using the AWS Management Console, AWS API, AWS CLI, AWS SDK, or AWS CloudFormation. Learn more at &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/vpc-interface-endpoints.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access AWS Billing and Cost Management using an interface endpoint (AWS PrivateLink)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-privatelink,general:products/cloud-financial-management</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-price-list-api-privatelink</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">971f8d55e6ec41125aa65b903624f7d30af057f5</guid>
			<title>Amazon SES now offers tiered pricing for Virtual Deliverability Manager</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Amazon &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ses/" target="_blank"&gt;Simple Email Service&lt;/a&gt; (SES) launched a new pricing structure for &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/ses/latest/dg/vdm.html" target="_blank"&gt;Virtual Deliverability Manager&lt;/a&gt; (VDM), giving customers reduced charges at higher levels of usage. Customers can benefit from lower total VDM charges without the need to change account configuration, sending practices, or billing setup. This can lower customer total cost of ownership for VDM as their usage increases.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Previously, all customers using VDM paid a fixed price per message sent. Customers could turn VDM on or off whenever needed, and they paid only for what they used without any commitment or fixed monthly charges. Now, customers will see their charges per message for VDM decrease as their sending volume exceeds specific thresholds each month. After crossing each threshold in a given billing month, each subsequent message processed by VDM is charged at a lower rate. This reduces the total cost of using VDM for high volume senders.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; SES supports tiered pricing for VDM in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS regions&lt;/a&gt; where SES is available.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For more information, see the documentation for the SES &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ses/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ses,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ses-tiered-pricing-virtual-deliverability-manager</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">cbe37870dd5c27e8b86cac0709ccc5c88efdc7a0</guid>
			<title>AWS Lambda adds application performance monitoring (APM) for Java and .NET runtimes via Application Signals</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Lambda now supports Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals, an application performance monitoring (APM) solution, for Java and .NET managed runtimes, enabling developers and operators to easily monitor the health and performance of their serverless applications built using Lambda.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We previously announced support for Application Signals for Lambda functions for Python and Node.js managed runtimes. With this launch, you can now enable Application Signals for Lambda functions using Java 11, Java 17, Java 21, and .NET 8 &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/lambda/latest/dg/lambda-runtimes.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Lambda managed runtimes&lt;/a&gt;. Once enabled, Application Signals provides pre-built, standardized dashboards for critical application metrics (such as throughput, availability, latency, faults, and errors), correlated traces, and interactions between the Lambda function and its dependencies (such as other AWS services), without requiring any manual instrumentation or code changes from developers. This gives operators a single-pane-of-glass view of the health of the application and enables them to drill down to establish the root cause of performance anomalies.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, visit the Configuration tab in Lambda console and enable Application Signals for your function with just one click in the “Monitoring and operational tools” section. To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/lambda/latest/dg/monitoring-application-signals.html" target="_blank"&gt;Lambda developer guide&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/CloudWatch-Application-Signals-Enable-Lambda.html" target="_blank"&gt;Application Signals developer guide&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/track-performance-of-serverless-applications-built-using-aws-lambda-with-application-signals/" target="_blank"&gt;Application Signals for Lambda blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Application Signals for Lambda is available in all commercial AWS Regions where Lambda and CloudWatch Application Signals are available. To take advantage of the new, cost-effective pricing for Application Signals, opt-in to the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/CloudWatch-Transaction-Search.html"&gt;Transaction Search&lt;/a&gt; capability of Application Signals. To learn more about Application Signals pricing, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;CloudWatch pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-lambda,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-lambda-adds-apm-java-net-runtimes-signals/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">adaa98412d1da9cbc91e1c7c5d2f82521592bf80</guid>
			<title>AWS CloudTrail network activity events for VPC endpoints are now generally available</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;With the launch of AWS CloudTrail network activity for VPC endpoints, you now have additional visibility into AWS API activity that traverses your VPC endpoints, enabling you to strengthen your data perimeter and implement better detective controls. You can enable network activity events for VPC endpoints for five AWS Services: Amazon S3, Amazon EC2, AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS), AWS Secrets Manager, and AWS CloudTrail.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With network activity events for VPC endpoints, you can view details of who is accessing resources within your network giving you greater ability to identify and respond to malicious or unauthorized actions in your data perimeter. For example, as the VPC endpoint owner, you can view logs of actions that were denied due to VPC endpoint policies or determine if an actor outside of your data perimeter is trying to access the data in your S3 buckets.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can enable logging for network activity events logging for your VPC endpoints using the AWS CloudTrail console, AWS CLI, and SDKs. When creating a new trail or event data store or editing an existing one, you can select network activity events for supported services that you wish to monitor; you can configure to log all API calls, or log only the accessDenied calls, and you can use advanced event selectors for additional filtering controls.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Network activity events for VPC endpoints are available in all commercial AWS Regions. Refer to &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;CloudTrail pricing&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about network activity events pricing and the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/logging-network-events-with-cloudtrail.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-cloudtrail,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-cloudtrail-network-activity-events-vpc-endpoints-generally-available</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">0096f0b821f147661ad98042eb5d325dc328a3be</guid>
			<title>Amazon Inspector enhances the security engine for container images scanning</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Amazon Inspector announced an upgrade to the engine powering its container image scanning for Amazon Elastic Container Registry (ECR). This upgrade will provide you with a more comprehensive view of the vulnerabilities in the third-party dependencies used in your container images. The enhancement to the engine will happen automatically without any action or disruption to your existing workflows. Existing customers can expect to see some findings closed as the new engine re-evaluates all the existing resources to better assess risks, while also surfacing new vulnerabilities as per the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/user/sbom-generator-dependency-collection.html" target="_blank"&gt;new engine’s dependency collection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Inspector&lt;/a&gt; is a vulnerability management service that continually scans AWS workloads including Amazon EC2 instances, container images, and AWS Lambda functions for software vulnerabilities, code vulnerabilities, and unintended network exposure across your entire AWS organization.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This improved version of container image scanning within ECR is available in all commercial and AWS GovCloud (US) Regions where &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Inspector is available&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/user/getting_started_tutorial.html" target="_blank"&gt;Getting started with Amazon Inspector&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Inspector free trial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-inspector,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/amazon-ecr</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-inspector-security-engine-container-images-scanning</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">0147d16bb66c29f5680a0627c7384e3fc7409e48</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 C7g instances are now available in the AWS Europe (Zurich) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C7g instances are available in the AWS Europe (Zurich) Region. These instances are powered by AWS Graviton3 processors that provide up to 25% better compute performance compared to AWS Graviton2 processors, and built on top of the the AWS Nitro System, a collection of AWS designed innovations that deliver efficient, flexible, and secure cloud services with isolated multi-tenancy, private networking, and fast local storage.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EC2 Graviton3 instances also use up to 60% less energy to reduce your cloud carbon footprint for the same performance than comparable EC2 instances. For increased scalability, these instances are available in 9 different instance sizes, including bare metal, and offer up to 30 Gbps networking bandwidth and up to 20 Gbps of bandwidth to the Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, see Amazon EC2 &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/c7g/" target="_blank"&gt;C7g&lt;/a&gt;. To explore how to migrate your workloads to Graviton-based instances, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/graviton/fast-start/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Graviton Fast Start program&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://github.com/aws/porting-advisor-for-graviton" target="_blank"&gt;Porting Advisor for Graviton&lt;/a&gt;. To get started, see the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/amazon-ec2</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-c7g-instances-zurich-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">edd874e683fdf42a089485038dd12e64f8f16464</guid>
			<title>Amazon Q Developer now supports upgrade to Java 21</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Q Developer transformation capabilities that allow customers to upgrade Java applications using Maven to Java 21 are now available. Developers interested in leveraging the enhanced performance, security, interoperability, and modern features of Java 21 can use the generative AI capabilities of Amazon Q Developer to accelerate code upgrades to Java 21.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this added support for Java Development Kit (JDK) 21, customers can upgrade the Java version of their applications using Maven from source versions 8, 11, 17, or 21 to target versions 17 or 21. Customers can also continue to upgrade libraries and frameworks used in Java 17 or Java 21 compatible applications without upgrading JDK versions. The Java transformation capabilities are available both in IDE (Visual Studio Code and JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA) and CLI (Linux and MacOS).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, please visit Amazon Q Developer transformation capabilities &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/q/developer/transform#Java" target="_blank"&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amazonq/latest/qdeveloper-ug/transform-java.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,general:products/amazon-q</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-q-developer-upgrade-java-21/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">584787955e02759c99383f20ed07194110aca79d</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 Capacity Blocks for ML is now available in several new regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Amazon Web Services announced that Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) Capacity Blocks for ML is now available in several new regions as well as new instance types in existing locations. You can use EC2 Capacity Blocks to reserve highly sought-after GPU instances in Amazon EC2 UltraClusters for a future date for the amount of time that you need to run your machine learning (ML) workloads.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; EC2 Capacity Blocks enable you to reserve GPU capacity up to eight weeks in advance for durations up to 6 months in cluster sizes of one to 64 instances, giving you the flexibility to run a broad range of ML workloads. They are ideal for short duration pre-training and fine-tuning workloads, rapid prototyping, and for handling surges in inference demand. EC2 Capacity Blocks deliver low-latency, high-throughput connectivity through colocation in Amazon EC2 UltraClusters.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this expansion, EC2 Capacity Blocks for ML are available on P5, P5e, P5en in US East (N. Virginia), US East (Ohio), US West (Oregon), US West (N. California), Europe (Stockholm), Europe (London), South America (Sao Paulo) Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Asia Pacific (Tokyo), Asia Pacific (Jakarta), Australia (Sydney), Australia (Melbourne) and P4d in US East (N. Virginia), US East (Ohio), US West (Oregon). Capacity Blocks are also available on Trn2 in US East (Ohio) and Trn1 in US East (N. Virginia), US East (Ohio), US West (Oregon), US West (N. California), Europe (Stockholm), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Australia (Sydney), Australia (Melbourne).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Click here to learn more about &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/capacityblocks/" target="_blank"&gt;EC2 Capacity Blocks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-capacity-blocks-ml-new-regions</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">34144d784e3bfe8a268f123730d12ed64c0ad24a</guid>
			<title>AWS Deadline Cloud now supports Adobe After Effects in Service-Managed Fleets</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Deadline Cloud now includes support for Adobe After Effects in its Service-Managed Fleets. AWS Deadline Cloud is a fully managed service that simplifies render management for teams creating computer-generated graphics and visual effects, created in industry-standard graphics tools such as Adobe After Effects, for films, television and broadcasting, web content, and design.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this new feature, you can submit After Effects projects to Deadline Cloud without having to manage your own render farm infrastructure. The integration offers built-in support for custom fonts and an adjustable number of image sequence frames rendered per task, allowing you to submit jobs that are tailored to your workflow directly within After Effects. AWS Deadline Cloud automatically handles the provisioning and elastic scaling of compute resources required for rendering your After Effects projects. Service-Managed Fleets can be configured in minutes so you can begin rendering immediately.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Deadline Cloud After Effects support is available in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where Deadline Cloud is offered.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For more information, please visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/deadline-cloud" target="_blank"&gt;Deadline Cloud product page&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/deadline-cloud/latest/userguide/supported-submitters.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Deadline Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-deadline-cloud,marketing:marchitecture/media-services</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-deadline-cloud-adobe-after-effects-service-managed-fleets</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e2b9ab0740c2a1715090398c09062b2034364a38</guid>
			<title>Amazon OpenSearch Serverless expands support for time-series workloads up to 100TB</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/features/serverless/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon OpenSearch Serverless&lt;/a&gt; now supports workloads up to 100TB of data for time-series collections. OpenSearch Serverless is a serverless deployment option for Amazon OpenSearch Service that makes it simple for you to run search and analytics workloads without having to think about infrastructure management. With the support for larger datasets, OpenSearch Serverless now enables more data-intensive use cases such as log analytics, security analytics, real-time application monitoring, and more.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; OpenSearch Serverless’ compute capacity used for indexing and search are measured in OpenSearch Compute Units (OCUs). To accommodate for larger datasets, OpenSearch Serverless now allows customers to independently scale indexing and search operations to use up to 1700 OCUs. You configure the maximum OCU limits on search and indexing independently to manage costs. You can also monitor real-time OCU usage with CloudWatch metrics to gain a better perspective on your workload's resource consumption.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Please refer to the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/opensearch-service.html#opensearch-service-regions" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regional Services List&lt;/a&gt; for more information about Amazon OpenSearch Service availability. To learn more about OpenSearch Serverless, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/latest/developerguide/serverless.html" target="_blank"&gt;see the documentation.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-opensearch-service,marketing:marchitecture/customer-enablement,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/serverless</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-opensearch-serverless-time-series-workloads-100tb</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">be0cf5915507126850bb9589ea001f5e5b81da2d</guid>
			<title>Introducing Amazon EC2 C6in instances in Chicago and New York City Local Zones</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C6in instances are now available in the Chicago and New York City Local Zones. C6in instances are powered by 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors with an all-core turbo frequency of up to 3.5 GHz. They are x86-based Amazon EC2 compute-optimized instances offering up to 200 Gbps of network bandwidth. The instances are built on AWS Nitro System, which is a dedicated and lightweight hypervisor that delivers the compute and memory resources of the host hardware to your instances for better overall performance and security. You can take advantage of the higher network bandwidth to scale the performance for a broad range of workloads running in AWS Local Zones.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Local Zones are an AWS infrastructure deployment that place compute, storage, database, and other select services closer to large population, industry, and IT centers where no AWS Region exists. You can use Local Zones to run applications that require single-digit millisecond latency for use cases such as real-time gaming, hybrid migrations, media and entertainment content creation, live video streaming, engineering simulations, financial services payment processing, capital market operations, and AR/VR.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, you can enable Chicago Local Zone us-east-1-chi-2a and New York City Local Zone us-east-1-nyc-2a , in the &lt;a href="https://us-east-1.console.aws.amazon.com/ec2/home?region=us-east-1#Settings:tab=zones;Category=local-zone" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EC2 Console&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/APIReference/API_ModifyAvailabilityZoneGroup.html" target="_blank"&gt;ModifyAvailabilityZoneGroup&lt;/a&gt; API, and deploy&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/c6i/" target="_blank"&gt; C6in instances&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more, visit &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/localzones/locations/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Local Zones overview page&lt;/a&gt; and see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EC2 Instance types&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/aws-local-zones,general:products/amazon-ec2</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-c6in-instances-chicago-new-york-city-local-zones</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">0b7a915f328afe8ffb5cf5fae6918dacc0f907d1</guid>
			<title>Amazon ECS now enables you to update services from short to long ARNs </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;You can now update your existing Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) services that use a short Amazon Resource Name (ARN) to use a long ARN without needing to re-create the service. This enables you to tag your long-running Amazon ECS services, letting you better allocate cost, improve visibility, and define fine-grained resource-level permissions for these services.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Since 2018, customers have been able to tag Amazon ECS services that use the long ARN format (which includes the cluster name in the ARN) but if they wanted to tag services that were created with the old short ARN format, they had to delete and re-create the service. Now, ECS enables you to tag services that were created with the old short ARN format without needing to re-create the service. To enable this, you need to complete 2 steps: 1/opt-in your account to the long Amazon Resource Names (ARN) format for tasks and services and 2/tag the service you want to migrate to the long ARN format using the TagResource API action. Once you complete these steps, ECS updates the ARN of the service to the long ARN format and tags the service. Updating the service to use the long ARN format allows you to define resource-based access policies in IAM and granularly monitor the cost of your services in the Cost &amp;amp; Usage Report and Cost Explorer.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can update your services with short ARNs to long ARNs in all AWS regions using the AWS Console, CLI, and API. To learn more, please read our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonECS/latest/developerguide/service-arn-migration.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/containers,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-ecs</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ecs-update-services-short-long-arns/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">264bd21b2c4e1e2a666472086b45fb0a2cfce54c</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 M7g instances are now available in additional regions </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) M7g instances are available in the AWS Asia Pacific (Jakarta, Melbourne, Osaka) and AWS GovCloud (US-East) regions. These instances are powered by AWS Graviton3 processors that provide up to 25% better compute performance compared to AWS Graviton2 processors, and built on top of the the AWS Nitro System, a collection of AWS designed innovations that deliver efficient, flexible, and secure cloud services with isolated multi-tenancy, private networking, and fast local storage.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EC2 Graviton3 instances also use up to 60% less energy to reduce your cloud carbon footprint for the same performance than comparable EC2 instances. For increased scalability, these instances are available in 9 different instance sizes, including bare metal, and offer up to 30 Gbps networking bandwidth and up to 20 Gbps of bandwidth to the Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, see Amazon EC2 &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/m7g/" target="_blank"&gt;M7g&lt;/a&gt;. To explore how to migrate your workloads to Graviton-based instances, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/graviton/fast-start/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Graviton Fast Start program&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://github.com/aws/porting-advisor-for-graviton" target="_blank"&gt;Porting Advisor for Graviton&lt;/a&gt;. To get started, see the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/amazon-ec2,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-m7g-instances-additional-regions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">8df226857b2a3c9e913897467642d26e8b5643b0</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for MySQL announces Extended Support minor 5.7.44-RDS.20250103</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/mysql/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)&lt;/a&gt; for MySQL announces Amazon RDS Extended Support minor version 5.7.44-RDS.20250103. We recommend that you upgrade to this version to fix known security vulnerabilities and bugs in prior versions of MySQL. Learn more about the bug fixes and patches in this version in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/MySQL.Concepts.VersionMgmt.html#mysql-extended-support-releases" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS Extended Support provides you more time, up to three years, to upgrade to a new major version to help you meet your business requirements. During Extended Support, Amazon RDS will provide critical security and bug fixes for your RDS for MySQL databases after the community ends support for a major version. You can run your MySQL databases on Amazon RDS with Extended Support for up to three years beyond a major version’s end of standard support date. Learn more about Extended Support in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/extended-support.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/mysql/pricing/#faqs:~:text=How%20can%20I%20estimate%20my%20RDS%20Extended%20Support%20charges%3F" target="_blank"&gt;Pricing FAQs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS for MySQL makes it simple to set up, operate, and scale MySQL deployments in the cloud. See &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/mysql/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for MySQL Pricing&lt;/a&gt; for pricing details and regional availability. Create or update a fully managed Amazon RDS database in the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/rds/home" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-rds-for-mysql,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-rds</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-mysql-extended-support-minor-5-7-44-rds-20250103</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">86af84a7154678b9cdcd2a09a35f94a80876dcf5</guid>
			<title>AWS CodePipeline adds CloudWatch Metrics support</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CodePipeline now provides Amazon CloudWatch metrics integration for V2 pipelines, enabling you to monitor both pipeline-level and account-level metrics directly in your AWS account. The integration introduces a pipeline duration metric that tracks the total execution time of your pipeline completions, and pipeline failure metric that monitors the frequency of pipeline execution failures. You can now track these metrics through both the CodePipeline console and the CloudWatch Metrics console to actively monitor your pipeline health.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about this feature, please visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/latest/userguide/metrics-dimensions.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. For more information about AWS CodePipeline, visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/codepipeline/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;. This feature is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all regions &lt;/a&gt;where AWS CodePipeline is supported, except the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions and the China Regions.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-codepipeline,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-codepipeline-cloudwatch-metrics-support/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">01ee5ba14ade472b29f80406f08e69afda522a27</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL supports minor versions 17.3, 16.7, 15.11, 14.16, 13.19</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/postgresql/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)&lt;/a&gt; for PostgreSQL now supports the latest minor versions 17.3, 16.7, 15.11, 14.16, and 13.19. We recommend that you upgrade to the latest minor versions to fix known security vulnerabilities in prior versions of PostgreSQL, and to benefit from the bug fixes added by the PostgreSQL community. This release also includes updates for PostgreSQL extensions such as pg_active 2.1.4, pg_cron 1.6.5, pg_partman 5.2.4, and others.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can use automatic minor version upgrades to automatically upgrade your databases to more recent minor versions during scheduled maintenance windows. You can also use &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/11/rds-blue-green-deployments-upgrade-rds-postgresql/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Blue/Green deployments&lt;/a&gt; for RDS for PostgreSQL using physical replication for your minor version upgrades. Learn more about upgrading your database instances, including automatic minor version upgrades and Blue/Green Deployments in the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_UpgradeDBInstance.PostgreSQL.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL makes it simple to set up, operate, and scale PostgreSQL deployments in the cloud. See &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/postgresql/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL Pricing&lt;/a&gt; for pricing details and regional availability. Create or update a fully managed Amazon RDS database in the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/rds/home" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-rds,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-for-postgresql-new-minor-versions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">dff82f5fcef73142f10c2e0ddb1ff8402ac19564</guid>
			<title>AWS Network Load Balancer now supports removing availability zones</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are launching the ability to remove Availability Zones (AZ) of an existing Network Load Balancer (NLB). Prior to this launch, customers could add AZs to an existing NLB, but could not remove AZs. With this capability, customers can now change their application stack locations and move them between availability zones quickly.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Changing business needs such as mergers &amp;amp; acquisitions, divestitures, data residency compliance requirements, and capacity considerations in a given region are some of the use cases that necessitate removing AZs of existing NLBs. Using this capability, customers can remove one or more availability zones from their NLB by simply updating the list of enabled subnets using ELB API, CLI or Console.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Similar to any delete operation, removing a zone can be a potentially disruptive operation. When you remove a zone, the NLB zonal Elastic Network Interface (ENI) is deleted. All active connections to backend targets in that zone (including clients connecting through other zones) are terminated, the zonal IPs (and EIPs) are released and zonal DNS names deleted, and any backend target in the removed zone becomes “unused”. Refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/latest/network/availability-zones.html" target="_blank"&gt;product documentation&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/networking-and-content-delivery/exploring-new-subnet-management-capabilities-of-network-load-balancer/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS blog post&lt;/a&gt; for prescriptive guidance on how to use this capability in a safe manner.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This capability is available in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS commercial&lt;/a&gt; and the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/networking,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-elastic-load-balancing</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-network-load-balancer-removing-availability-zones</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1f08457d13f323558e50e353ae3f4ab3f3d1c732</guid>
			<title>Amazon Q generative SQL is now available in additional regions </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Q generative SQL is now available in Amazon Redshift Query Editor for US East (Ohio) and Asia Pacific (Seoul) regions. This feature enhances SQL query authoring in the web-based Query Editor for Amazon Redshift, enabling you to write SQL queries using natural language and receive intelligent SQL code recommendations. Amazon Q generative SQL makes Amazon Redshift database querying more accessible and efficient for users, regardless of their SQL expertise.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Using generative AI, Amazon Q generative SQL analyzes user intent, SQL query patterns, and schema metadata to identify common query patterns within Amazon Redshift. The conversational interface allows users to submit SQL queries in natural language while maintaining their existing data permissions. For example, when asking "Find total revenue by region," the system automatically suggests appropriate SQL code by joining relevant Amazon Redshift tables, reducing development time and potential errors. Users can accept suggested queries directly or iterate with follow-up questions to refine their results.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about pricing, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/q/developer/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Q Developer pricing page&lt;/a&gt;. See the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/query-editor-v2-generative-ai.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; to get started.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,marketing:marchitecture/analytics,general:products/amazon-q</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-q-generative-sql-additional-regions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">72c9212c6f5da6f1f6ca6492793241697bc3f47b</guid>
			<title>Amazon FSx for Lustre now supports Lustre version upgrades</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/fsx/lustre/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon FSx for Lustre&lt;/a&gt;, a service that provides high-performance, cost-effective, and scalable file storage for compute workloads, now enables you to upgrade the Lustre version of your FSx for Lustre file systems. This feature allows you to benefit from the enhancements available in newer Lustre versions on your existing file systems.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; FSx for Lustre provides fully-managed file systems built on Lustre, the world's most popular open-source high performance file system. FSx for Lustre supports multiple long-term support Lustre versions released by the Lustre community. Newer Lustre versions provide benefits such as performance enhancements, new features, and support for the latest Linux kernel versions for your client instances. Starting today, you can upgrade your file systems to newer Lustre versions within minutes using the AWS management console or the AWS CLI/SDK .&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The feature is now available on all file systems at no additional cost in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where FSx for Lustre is available. For more information, see Amazon FSx for Lustre &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/fsx/latest/LustreGuide/what-is.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-fsx-for-lustre,marketing:marchitecture/storage</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-fsx-lustre-lustre-version-upgrades</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">9351c0d9b54d700c07b2aefcfc313595c042c8ea</guid>
			<title>AWS AppSync enhances resolver testing with comprehensive context object mocking</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS AppSync, a fully managed GraphQL service that helps customers build scalable APIs, announces improvements to its EvaluateCode and EvaluateMappingTemplate APIs. This update enables developers to comprehensively mock all properties of the context object during resolver and function unit testing, including identity information, stash variables, and error handling. The enhancement also introduces improved JSON input validation with clear, actionable error messages, making it easier for developers to identify and fix issues in their context setup.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These improvements simplify the setup and configuration requirements. Developers can now efficiently test functions and resolvers by accessing and validating resolver stash (ctx.stash) and error tracking (ctx.outErrors) in their test environments. The update also simplifies identity mocking by allowing developers to include only the relevant caller information in ctx.identity. The updated console experience provides better visibility into the resolver test results, helping developers troubleshoot and optimize their resolver implementations more effectively.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This enhancement is available in all AWS Regions where AWS AppSync is currently supported.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt; To learn more about these new features, visit the AWS AppSync&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/appsync/latest/devguide/resolver-reference-overview-js.html"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and explore the context object&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/appsync/latest/devguide/resolver-context-reference-js.html" target="_blank"&gt;reference&lt;/a&gt;. You can also explore examples and best practices in the AWS AppSync Developer Guide or get started by visiting the AWS AppSync console.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-appsync,marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-appsync-resolver-testing-comprehensive-context-object-mocking</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">158229aeb316d61b65dae6e44b16ff120b070433</guid>
			<title>AWS HealthScribe now supports GIRPP note template for behavioral health</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS HealthScribe is a generative AI-powered service that automatically generates summarized clinical notes and transcripts from patient-clinician conversations. Documentation for behavioral health related encounters follows a goal centric format based on GIRPP (Goal, Intervention, Response, Progress, Plan) format. With this launch, AWS HealthScribe customers can directly convert a behavioral health related patient-clinician conversation to a GIRPP format note. This can potentially save clinicians hours daily in manually documenting behavioral health related encounters.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers using the HealthScribe StartMedicalScribeJob and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/transcribe/latest/APIReference/API_streaming_StartMedicalScribeStream.html" target="_blank"&gt;StartMedicalScribeStream&lt;/a&gt; API can simply set note template type parameter as “GIRPP” in the ClinicalNoteGenerationSettings for both async and streaming jobs and will share the output note in GIRPP format as the conversation ends.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in US East (N.Virginia) Region. To learn more refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/transcribe/latest/dg/health-scribe.html" target="_blank"&gt;our documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-healthscribe-girpp-note-template-behavioral-health</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f6073cc038cc636af2924a06da28d23d246e02af</guid>
			<title>Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) now adds full snapshot size information in Console and API</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) now displays the full snapshot size for EBS Snapshots. With this enhancement, customers can now retrieve full snapshot sizes programmatically through the DescribeSnapshots API using the new field, full-snapshot-size-in-bytes. The full snapshot size is also displayed in the EBS Snapshots console under the new 'Full snapshot size' column.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Since EBS Snapshots are incremental in nature, if you take multiple snapshots of a volume over time, each snapshot only stores the new or modified blocks while maintaining references to unchanged blocks from previous snapshots.&lt;br&gt; The ‘full snapshot size’ field shows you the total size of all blocks that make up a snapshot, including both the blocks stored directly in that snapshot and all blocks referenced from previous snapshots. For instance, if you have a 100 GB volume with 50 GB of data, the ‘full snapshot size’ would show 50 GB regardless of whether it's the first snapshot or a subsequent one.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The ‘full snapshot size’ field provides crucial information about your EBS snapshot storage, such as the total size of the snapshot in the archived tier or the amount of data written to the source volume at the time the snapshot was created. Please note that this is different from the incremental snapshot size, which only refers to the size of newly changed blocks stored in that specific snapshot.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is now generally available in all commercial AWS regions and the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. To get started, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/ebs/latest/userguide/ebs-snapshots.html" target="_blank"&gt;EBS Snapshots user guide&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/APIReference/API_DescribeSnapshots.html" target="_blank"&gt;API specification&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/amazon-elastic-block-store</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ebs-full-snapshot-size-information-console-api</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">54f1252748a570aa891e4ce422769c7bc97fd58c</guid>
			<title>Amazon Polly launches a new voice in Singaporean English</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are excited to announce the general availability of Jasmine - new Singaporean English Neural Text-to-Speech (NTTS) female voice for Amazon Polly.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/polly" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Polly&lt;/a&gt; is a service that turns text into lifelike speech, allowing you to create applications that talk and to build entirely new categories of speech-enabled products.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Jasmine is our first voice for the Singaporean variant of English. Even though Singaporean English is reported to be close to British English, there are some unique pronunciation patterns that we captured while training this voice, such as pronunciation of telephone numbers or postal codes, to make sure that Jasmine sounds like a local speaker. With this launch, we continue building a variety of voice and language options for Amazon Polly customers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Jasmine and all the other NTTS voices are available in &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/polly/latest/dg/NTTS-main.html#ntts-regions" target="_blank"&gt;AWS regions supporting Neural TTS&lt;/a&gt;. For more details, please read the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/polly/latest/dg/what-is.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Polly documentation&lt;/a&gt; and visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/polly/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-polly,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-polly-new-voice-singaporean-english</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">196ed37ccd7b7bcd9a26b6a56c93538143efe812</guid>
			<title>AWS AppSync GraphQL introduces operation-level caching for faster GraphQL API responses</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS AppSync GraphQL now offers operation-level caching, a new feature that allows customers to cache entire GraphQL query operation responses. This enhancement enables developers to optimize read-heavy GraphQL APIs, delivering faster response times and improved application performance.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Operation-level caching in AWS AppSync GraphQL streamlines the caching process by storing complete query responses. This approach is particularly beneficial for complex queries or high-traffic scenarios, where it can significantly reduce latency and enhance the overall user experience. By caching at the operation level, developers can easily boost API efficiency and create more responsive applications without additional code changes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Operation-level caching is now available in all AWS Regions where AWS AppSync is offered.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about operation-level caching in AWS AppSync GraphQL, visit the AWS AppSync &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/appsync/latest/devguide/enabling-caching.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. You can start using this feature today by configuring caching settings in the AWS AppSync GraphQL console or through the AWS CLI.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/messaging,general:products/aws-appsync</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-appsync-graphql-operation-level-caching-api-responses</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f136ced2b86eef76e0080937a696c98f0ca12d58</guid>
			<title>Amazon Connect Contact Lens can now take automated actions based on hold times and agent interaction time</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Connect Contact Lens now enables managers to create rules based on patterns of customer hold time and agent interaction duration, to take automated actions such as categorizing contacts, evaluating agent performance and notifying supervisors. With this launch, managers can create rules to check how well agents comply with guidelines on placing customers on hold. For example, did the agent set expectations on hold duration, before placing the customer on hold for more than 5 minutes? In addition, managers can check if the agent interaction lasted long enough to warrant assessment of complex agent behaviors such as building customer rapport, customer issue root cause analysis, etc. By excluding contacts that were too short, such as less than 30 seconds, managers can get more meaningful insights from automated contact categorization and agent performance evaluations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all regions where Contact Lens performance evaluations are already available. To learn more, please visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/connect/latest/adminguide/build-rules-for-contact-lens.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/contact-lens/" target="_blank"&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt;. For information about Contact Lens pricing, please visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity,general:products/amazon-connect</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-connect-contact-lens-automated-actions-based-hold-times-agent-interaction-time</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">08c3954fcfa78711c3437e0aa58ddb8ca47a7a8a</guid>
			<title>Amazon Connect Contact Lens now provides a dashboard with aggregated insights on agent performance evaluations</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Contact Lens now provides managers with an agent performance evaluation dashboard, to view aggregations of agent performance, and insights across cohorts of agents over time. With this launch, managers can access a unified dashboard on agent performance across evaluation scores, productivity (e.g., contacts handled, average handle time, etc.) and operational metrics. Through detailed performance scorecards at both team and individual levels, managers can dive deep into specific performance criteria, and compare performance with similar cohorts and over time, to identify agent strengths and improvement opportunities. The dashboard also provides managers with insights into agent time allocation and contact handling efficiency, so they can drive improvements in agent productivity.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all regions where Contact Lens performance evaluations are already available. To learn more, please visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/connect/latest/adminguide/agent-performance-evaluation-dashboard.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/contact-lens/" target="_blank"&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt;. For information about Contact Lens pricing, please visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/messaging,general:products/amazon-connect</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-connect-contact-lens-dashboard-agent-evaluations/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">903645d9c70bf6a4bd566049a4962d7863a327c8</guid>
			<title>Amazon DynamoDB now supports auto-approval of quota adjustments</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;You can now request for Amazon DynamoDB account-level and table-level throughput quota adjustments using AWS &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/servicequotas/latest/userguide/intro.html" target="_blank"&gt;Service Quotas&lt;/a&gt; in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Commercial Regions&lt;/a&gt; and the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions, and get auto-approved within minutes.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Previously, when requesting a quota adjustment, Service Quotas allowed you to indicate the Amazon DynamoDB quota and desired value to be adjusted to. AWS Support would then review your request, approve, and make the adjustments. With this launch, when you make updates to your DynamoDB account-level and table-level throughput quotas using AWS Service Quotas, your adjustments will get automatically approved and adjusted with just a few clicks. AWS Service Quotas is available at no additional charge.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about Amazon DynamoDB, the Serverless, NoSQL, fully managed database with single-digit millisecond performance at any scale, please visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon DynamoDB website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-dynamodb,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-dynamodb-supports-auto-approval-quota-adjustments/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">d8e41edf96e70281edcc6b4dce8f22d020cc5796</guid>
			<title>AWS Secrets and Configuration Provider now integrates with Pod Identity for Amazon EKS</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/secrets-manager/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Secrets Manager&lt;/a&gt; announces that AWS Secrets and Configuration Provider (ASCP) now integrates with Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) Pod Identity. This integration simplifies IAM authentication for Amazon EKS when retrieving secrets from AWS Secrets Manager or parameters from AWS Systems Manager Parameter Store. With this new capability, you can manage IAM permissions for Kubernetes applications more efficiently and securely, enabling granular access control through role session tags on secrets.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; ASCP is a plugin for the industry-standard Kubernetes Secrets Store CSI Driver. It enables applications running in Kubernetes pods to retrieve secrets from AWS Secrets Manager easily, without the need for custom code or restarting containers when secrets are rotated. The AWS EKS Pod Identity, streamlines the process of configuring IAM permissions for Kubernetes applications in a more efficient and secure way. This integration combines the strengths of both components, enhancing secret management in Amazon EKS environments.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Previously, ASCP relied on &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/eks/latest/userguide/iam-roles-for-service-accounts.html" target="_blank"&gt;IAM Roles for Service Accounts (IRSA)&lt;/a&gt; for authentication. Now, you can choose between IRSA and Pod Identity for IAM authentication using the new optional parameter "usePodIdentity". This flexibility allows you to adopt the authentication method that best suits your security requirements and operational needs.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The integration of ASCP with Pod Identity is available in all AWS Regions where AWS Secrets Manager and Amazon EKS Pod Identity are supported. To get started with this new feature, see the following resources &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/secretsmanager/latest/userguide/integrate_eks.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Secrets Manager documentation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/eks/latest/userguide/pod-identities.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EKS Pod Identity &lt;/a&gt;documentation and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/security/announcing-ascp-integration-with-pod-identity-enhanced-security-for-secrets-management-in-amazon-eks/" target="_blank"&gt;launch blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-secrets-manager,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-secrets-configuration-provider-pod-identity-eks/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">91ca46f16327753d615fed58eb5b72b42a2536d7</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 M8g instances now available in AWS Europe (London)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) M8g instances are available in AWS Europe (London) region. These instances are powered by AWS Graviton4 processors and deliver up to 30% better performance compared to AWS Graviton3-based instances. Amazon EC2 M8g instances are built for general-purpose workloads, such as application servers, microservices, gaming servers, midsize data stores, and caching fleets. These instances are built on the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/nitro/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Nitro System&lt;/a&gt;, which oﬄoads CPU virtualization, storage, and networking functions to dedicated hardware and software to enhance the performance and security of your workloads.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS Graviton4-based Amazon EC2 instances deliver the best performance and energy efficiency for a broad range of workloads running on Amazon EC2. These instances offer larger instance sizes with up to 3x more vCPUs and memory compared to Graviton3-based Amazon M7g instances. AWS Graviton4 processors are up to 40% faster for databases, 30% faster for web applications, and 45% faster for large Java applications than AWS Graviton3 processors. M8g instances are available in 12 different instance sizes, including two bare metal sizes. They offer up to 50 Gbps enhanced networking bandwidth and up to 40 Gbps of bandwidth to the Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/m8g/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EC2 M8g Instances&lt;/a&gt;. To explore how to migrate your workloads to Graviton-based instances, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/graviton/fast-start/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Graviton Fast Start program&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://github.com/aws/porting-advisor-for-graviton" target="_blank"&gt;Porting Advisor for Graviton&lt;/a&gt;. To get started, see the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-m8g-instances-aws-europe-london</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">a209e6092db87d541758d7809bd64ffc5e9430d8</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for SQL Server supports new minor version in January 2025</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;A new minor version of Microsoft SQL Server is now available on &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/sqlserver/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for SQL Server&lt;/a&gt;, providing performance enhancements and security fixes. Amazon RDS for SQL Server now supports this latest minor version of SQL Server 2022 across the Express, Web, Standard, and Enterprise editions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; We encourage you to upgrade your Amazon RDS for SQL Server database instances at your convenience. You can upgrade with just a few clicks in the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/rds/home" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS Management Console&lt;/a&gt; or by using the AWS CLI. Learn more about upgrading your database instances from the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_UpgradeDBInstance.SQLServer.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS User Guide&lt;/a&gt;. The new minor version is SQL Server 2022 CU17 - 16.0.4175.1.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This minor version is available in all &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/Concepts.RegionsAndAvailabilityZones.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS commercial regions&lt;/a&gt; where Amazon RDS for SQL Server databases are available, including the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon RDS for SQL Server makes it simple to set up, operate, and scale SQL Server deployments in the cloud. See &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/sqlserver/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for SQL Server Pricing&lt;/a&gt; for pricing details and regional availability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-rds-for-sql-server,general:products/amazon-rds,general:products/aws-govcloud-us</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-sql-server-minor-version-january-2025</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">45e745f49c8fa8d0350a939145d924009e8a10ee</guid>
			<title>Amazon CloudWatch now provides lock contention diagnostics for Aurora PostgreSQL</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon CloudWatch Database Insights now provides lock contention diagnostics for Aurora PostgreSQL instances. This feature helps you identify the root cause behind both ongoing and historical lock contention issues within minutes. The lock contention diagnostics feature is available exclusively in the Advanced mode of CloudWatch Database Insights.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this launch, you can visualize a locking condition in the Database Insights console, which shows the relationship between blocking and waiting sessions. The visualization helps you quickly identify the dominating sessions, queries, or objects causing lock contention. Additionally, this feature persists historical locking data for 15 months, allowing you to analyze and investigate historical locking conditions. You no longer need to manually run custom queries or rely on application logs to diagnose lock contention issues, streamlining the troubleshooting process.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can get started with this feature by enabling the Advanced mode of CloudWatch Database Insights on your Aurora PostgreSQL clusters using the Aurora service console, AWS APIs, or the AWS SDK. CloudWatch Database Insights delivers database health monitoring aggregated at the fleet level, as well as instance-level dashboards for detailed database and SQL query analysis.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; CloudWatch Database Insights is available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;all public AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; and offers vCPU-based pricing – see the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt; for details. For further information, visit the&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/Database-Insights.html" target="_blank"&gt; Database Insights documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/amazon-aurora,general:products/amazon-rds</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-cloudwatch-lock-contention-diagnostics-aurora-postgresql</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">cb888bd8fef564250911956e7e266b17aac58acb</guid>
			<title>Amazon Redshift Serverless announces reduction in IP Address Requirements to 3 per Subnet</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Redshift Serverless announces reduction in IP Address Requirements to 3 per Subnet. When using Amazon Redshift Serverless without Enhanced VPC Routing (EVR) enabled, you only need 3 free IP addresses in each subnet in your Amazon VPC. The new enhancement makes starting with &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/redshift-serverless/"&gt;Amazon Redshift Serverless&lt;/a&gt; easier, and you do not have to worry about free IP addresses in your Amazon VPC subnet network.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Before this announcement, you must have at least 9 free IP addresses in your subnet when creating an Amazon Redshift Serverless workgroup (workgroup) or when updating your workgroup for the Redshift Processing Units (RPUs), you must have at least 10 free IP addresses in your subnets. With this announcement, you only need 3 free IP addresses in your subnets when creating or updating the workgroup without EVR regardless of the size of the base RPU (8 to 1024 RPUs) or the RPU usage of your workgroup or workgroups enabled with AI-driven scaling and optimizations. Any existing workgroup will also benefit from the decreased IP address needs, regardless of the base RPU size or RPU usage, and including workgroups enabled with AI-driven scaling and optimizations.&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;Your administrative overhead is reduced when RPUs for your workgroup increase as the free IP address requirements are reduced significantly, and you do not need to take steps to free up IP addresses.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The need for 3 free IP addresses in Amazon Redshift Serverless applies to all commercial &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS regions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/govcloud-us/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS GovCloud (US) Regions&lt;/a&gt; where Amazon Redshift Serverless is available.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Refer to this &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/serverless-usage-considerations.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation &lt;/a&gt;to learn more about the free IP address in Amazon Redshift Serverless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/amazon-redshift,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-redshift-serverless-ip-address-3-per-subnet/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">b79f2bd1c1dc229c432ff5a57d149a2266dc2663</guid>
			<title>Anthropic’s upgraded Claude 3.5 Sonnet now available in the Asia Pacific (Sydney) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Anthropic’s upgraded Claude 3.5 Sonnet model is now available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; in the Asia Pacific (Sydney) AWS Region. According to Anthropic, the model delivers across-the-board improvements over its predecessor, with significant gains in coding—an area where it already led the field.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The upgraded Claude 3.5 Sonnet model shows wide-ranging improvements on industry benchmarks. On coding the model improves performance on SWE-bench Verified from 33% to 49%. It also improves performance on TAU-bench, an agentic tool use task, from 62.6% to 69.2% in the retail domain, and from 36.0% to 46.0% in the airline domain. The model offers these advancements at the same price of its predecessor. Additionally, Claude 3.5 Sonnet now offers computer use capabilities in Amazon Bedrock in public beta, allowing Claude to perceive and interact with computer interfaces. Developers can direct Claude to use computers the way people do—by looking at a screen, moving a cursor, clicking buttons, and typing text. Given this technology is early stage, developers are encouraged to explore lower-risk tasks.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, read the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/upgraded-claude-3-5-sonnet-from-anthropic-available-now-computer-use-public-beta-and-claude-3-5-haiku-coming-soon-in-amazon-bedrock" target="_blank"&gt;AWS News launch blog&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/claude/" target="_blank"&gt;Claude in Amazon Bedrock product page&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/model-parameters-claude.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. To get started with Claude, visit the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Bedrock console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-bedrock,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-machine-learning</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/anthropics-upgraded-claude-3-5-sonnet-sydney-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">ec41a143ad75914688baf9d75ea792978ce90edb</guid>
			<title>Amazon EFS now supports up to 10,000 access points per EFS file system</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/efs/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Elastic File System&lt;/a&gt; (Amazon EFS) has now increased the access points limit from 1,000 to 10,000 per file system, a 10x increase. This launch makes it even easier for customers to manage application-specific access to shared datasets, enabling them to seamlessly scale access management to thousands of users, on a single EFS file system.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EFS is a fully elastic file storage service that makes it simple to set up and run file workloads in the AWS cloud. Access points are application-specific entry points that enforce a user identity and root directory, and logically isolate data between applications. The new EFS access point limits automatically apply to all file systems and require no action from customers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The new access point limits are immediately available in all commercial AWS regions, except in AWS China Regions. To learn more, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/efs/latest/ug/efs-access-points.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EFS Documentation&lt;/a&gt; or create a file system using the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/efs" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EFS Console&lt;/a&gt;, API, or AWS CLI.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/amazon-efs</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-efs-access-points-file-system/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">581ea04057be7a7a8b7acd4476c5302247de8ca3</guid>
			<title>CloudWatch Application Signals now supports Runtime Metrics for .NET Applications</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS is announcing the general availability of runtime metrics for .NET applications in Amazon CloudWatch Application Signals, an OpenTelemetry (OTel)-compatible application performance monitoring (APM) feature in CloudWatch. Without requiring any source code changes, you can now collect runtime metrics such as Garbage Collection and Heap usage from .NET applications and correlate with application metrics, traces, and logs for applications running across EKS, EC2, ECS and on-premise servers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Runtime metrics enable real-time monitoring of your application’s resource consumption, such as memory and CPU usage. Now, for .NET applications, developers and SREs can determine whether anomalies in runtime metrics affect key application metrics—such as errors, latency, and throughput. For example, they can identify if a service latency spike is a result of an increase in garbage collection pauses by viewing these metric graphs side by side. Additionally you will be able to identify thread contention, track memory allocation patterns, and pinpoint memory or CPU spikes that may lead to application slowdown, impacting end-user experience.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Runtime metrics support is available for Java, Python and now .NET applications across all regions Application Signals is available in.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; See &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/AppSignals-MetricsCollected.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about the standard and runtime metrics collected by Application Signals. Don’t forget to opt in to the new, cost-effective pricing for Application Signals. For more details, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon CloudWatch pricing page&lt;/a&gt; and look for the &lt;em&gt;“Application Signals &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(including complete visibility into application transaction spans)”&lt;/em&gt; section.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/amazon-cloudwatch</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/cloudwatch-application-signals-runtime-metrics-net-applications/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">c038129468dc318429789536482322d077b8c51e</guid>
			<title>Announcing AWS CloudFormation support for AWS Transfer Family web apps</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;You can now use AWS CloudFormation templates to create and manage your AWS Transfer Family web apps. This enables you to define and deploy Transfer Family web apps via infrastructure-as-code so you can automate centralized management at scale.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With CloudFormation templates, you can programmatically provision and configure your Transfer Family web app, associated customizations, and S3 access grants in a single deployment. This eliminates time-consuming manual configurations and ensures you maintain consistent, secure implementations across departments. You can rapidly scale your file transfer interfaces from hundreds to thousands of users while maintaining strict security and compliance standards through version-controlled infrastructure templates.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS CloudFormation support is available &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/transfer/latest/userguide/web-app.html#webapp-regions" target="_blank"&gt;in all regions where Transfer Family web apps are available&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more about Transfer Family web apps, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/transfer/latest/userguide/web-app.html" target="_blank"&gt;Transfer Family User Guide&lt;/a&gt; and read our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-aws-transfer-family-web-apps-for-fully-managed-amazon-s3-file-transfers/" target="_blank"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;. For sample templates and detailed documentation, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/AWS_Transfer.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS CloudFormation documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/migration,general:products/aws-cloudformation,general:products/aws-transfer-family</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-cloudformation-aws-transfer-family-web-apps</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">a63466a33cba5606f378c83ac9d072b5e368eb8a</guid>
			<title>AWS Step Functions expands data source and output options for Distributed Map</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Step Functions now supports additional data sources and output options for Distributed Map, enabling more flexible large-scale parallel processing workflows. Distributed map can now process data from JSON Lines (JSONL) and a broader range of delimited file formats stored in Amazon S3. Additionally, distributed map offers new output transformations for greater control over result formatting.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/step-functions/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Step Functions&lt;/a&gt; is a visual workflow service capable of orchestrating over 14,000+ API actions from over 220 AWS services to build distributed applications and data processing workloads. With this update, you can more easily iterate over and process diverse datasets using Step Functions distributed map. In addition to existing JSON and comma separated value (CSV) file support, distributed map now supports JSONL, and new delimited file formats, such as semicolon-delimited files and tab-delimited files. This expands processing capabilities to a wider range of data formats without custom pre-processing. The new flexible output transformations give you more control over how results are formatted, enabling easier aggregation of results and simplifying integration with downstream systems.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To get started, you can use the distributed map mode today in the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/states/home/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Step Functions console&lt;/a&gt; or read this &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/compute/introducing-jsonl-support-with-step-functions-distributed-map/" target="_blank"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more, visit the Step Functions &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/step-functions/latest/dg/input-output-fields-dist-map.html" target="_blank"&gt;developer guide.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-step-functions,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-step-functions-data-source-output-option-distributed-map</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f8b0cc81af832c3438ce7adf604737cf44bdd269</guid>
			<title>Amazon FSx now supports Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6) on FSx Service APIs</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon FSx now offers customers the option to use Internet Protocol version 6 (IPv6) while accessing the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/fsxn.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon FSx Service APIs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; More and more customers are adopting IPv6 to mitigate IPv4 address exhaustion in their private networks or to satisfy government mandates such as such as the US Office of Management and Budget (OMB) M-21-07 memorandum. With this launch, customers can standardize their applications and workflows for managing their Amazon FSx resources on the new version of Internet Protocol by using the new dual-stack Amazon FSx Service endpoints.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; IPv6 support for Amazon FSx Service APIs is available in all commercial, AWS GovCloud (US), and AWS China regions where Amazon FSx is available. To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/fsx/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon FSx user guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/amazon-fsx-for-openzfs</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-fsx-supports-ipv6-fsx-service-apis/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">40fe7d30dc87758ae5b8b0c486d8ed4489081e42</guid>
			<title>Announcing custom payment schedules for AWS Marketplace Channel Partner private offers</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Marketplace now supports custom payment schedules for private offers, giving Channel Partners the ability to add margins on private offers with installment plans. Channel Partners can now adjust each scheduled payment individually, either through the AWS Marketplace Management Portal or the AWS Marketplace Catalog API.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Previously, Channel Partners could only apply a uniform percentage markup across all installments in a private offer. With this update, they can now adjust the payment amount for each installment in the schedule, providing greater flexibility in structuring deals and managing cash flow. Once the buyer accepts and pays their invoices, the Channel Partner and independent software vendor (ISV) will receive their appropriate payment as defined in the offer and resell agreement. This saves Channel Partners significant time and effort, eliminating the need to request margin updates from AWS.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Channel Partners can use this feature for all AWS Marketplace products using installment plans sold through Channel Partner private offers, across all &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/marketplace/latest/buyerguide/buyer-paying-for-products.html" target="_blank"&gt;supported currencies&lt;/a&gt;. This feature is available in all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where AWS Marketplace is available.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/marketplace/latest/userguide/agreements-overview.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Marketplace Seller Guide&lt;/a&gt;. To try the new capability, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace/management/offers/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Marketplace Management Portal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-marketplace,marketing:marchitecture/partner-network,marketing:marchitecture/aws-marketplace-and-partners</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/custom-payment-schedules-marketplace-partner-offers/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">cf83ab4c22c9754478c72a06f9a2d3882607bb55</guid>
			<title>Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager now supports Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager now offers customers the option to use Internet Protocol version 6 (IPv6) addresses for their new and existing endpoints. Customers moving to IPv6 can simplify their networks stack by running their Data Lifecycle Manager dual-stack endpoints on a network supporting both IPv4 and IPv6, depending on the protocol used by their network and client.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers create Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager policies to automate the creation, retention, and management of EBS Snapshots and EBS-backed Amazon Machine Images (AMIs). The policies can also automatically copy created resources across AWS Regions, move EBS Snapshots to EBS Snapshots Archive tier, and manage Fast Snapshot Restore. Customers can also create policies to automate creation and retention of application-consistent EBS Snapshots via pre and post-scripts, as well as create Default Policies for comprehensive protection for their account or AWS Organization.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager with IPv6 is now available in all AWS commercial Regions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about configuring Amazon Data Lifecycle Manager endpoints for IPv6, please refer to our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/ebs/latest/userguide/dlm-service-endpoints.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/amazon-elastic-block-store</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-data-lifecycle-manager-supports-ipv6/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">438bf3fbf01fe288217d0054e736393afb2de732</guid>
			<title>AWS Config now supports 4 new resource types</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Config now supports 4 additional AWS resource types. This expansion provides greater coverage over your AWS environment, enabling you to more effectively discover, assess, audit, and remediate an even broader range of resources.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this launch, if you have enabled recording for all resource types, then AWS Config will automatically track these new additions. The newly supported resource types are also available in Config rules and Config aggregators.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;You can now use AWS Config to monitor the following newly supported resource types in all &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/config/latest/developerguide/what-is-resource-config-coverage.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where the supported resources are available:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;AWS::EC2::VPCBlockPublicAccessExclusion&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;AWS::EC2::VPCBlockPublicAccessOptions&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;AWS::S3Express::BucketPolicy&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;AWS::S3Express::DirectoryBucket&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;To view the complete list of AWS Config supported resource types, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/config/latest/developerguide/resource-config-reference.html" target="_blank"&gt;supported resource types&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-config,marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-config-4-new-resource-types/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2be0d4885aa2654b532fe3ec99adc10788ea1da6</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances are now available in Seoul (Asia Pacific) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon EC2 U7in-8tb instances are now available in the Seoul (Asia Pacific) region. U7in-8tb instances are part of AWS 7th generation and are powered by custom fourth generation Intel Xeon Scalable Processors (Sapphire Rapids), delivering up to 135% more compute performance over existing U-1 instances. U7in-8tb instances offer 8TiB of DDR5 memory enabling customers to scale transaction processing throughput in a fast-growing data environment.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; U7in-8tb instances offer 448 vCPUs, support up to 60Gbps Elastic Block Storage (EBS) for faster data loading and backups, deliver up to 100Gbps of network bandwidth, and support ENA Express. U7i instances are ideal for customers using mission-critical in-memory databases like SAP HANA, Oracle, and SQL Server.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about U7i instances, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/u7i/" target="_blank"&gt;High Memory instances page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-high-memory-u7i-instances-seoul/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">62f423adfb6e7b7f07d4eb6b8c1ea047438c6885</guid>
			<title>AWS WAF Console adds new top insights visualizations in additional regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS WAF’s console dashboard now includes richer visualizations that give you insights into the top sources of traffic in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. With this feature, customers with CloudWatch logging destinations can view a new top insights section within the all traffic dashboard.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers previously used the all traffic dashboard, a default dashboard that populates visualizations based on CloudWatch metrics. As customers strive to continue gaining additional visibility into their traffic, they have requested richer visualizations based on logs in addition to visualizations based on CloudWatch metrics.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Starting today, customers with CloudWatch logging destinations will have access to this new top insights section within the all traffic dashboard, which includes richer visualizations based on terminating rules, client IPs, URI path, and more. These top insights will enable customers to better understand their security posture, quickly identify anomalies, and optimize their WAF configurations accordingly. For example, if a customer sees more than expected traffic from an suspicious IP address, they can take steps to create a IP-blocking rule to address this anomaly.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Standard CloudWatch pricing applies to metrics and logs queried through the dashboard. For more information about pricing, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS CloudWatch Pricing page&lt;/a&gt;. The feature is now available in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions for all origin types supported by WAF. For more information about the all traffic dashboard, visit the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/waf-chapter.html" target="_blank"&gt;Developer Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-waf</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-waf-console-top-insights-visualizations-additional-regions</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">64a26b54f803a6e9c08e3006fbf66a293ea7231c</guid>
			<title>AWS IAM Identity Center now offers improved error messages and AWS CloudTrail logging for provisioning issues</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS IAM Identity Center now provides improved error messages to simplify troubleshooting when syncing users and groups. You can also build automated monitoring and auditing for these errors using the AWS CloudTrail logs.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; IAM Identity Center helps you securely connect your workforce identities and manage their access centrally across AWS accounts and applications. With improved error messaging, IAM Identity Center provides actionable information to troubleshoot provisioning issues as you sync your users and groups using SCIM or configurable AD sync. CloudTrail logs enable automated monitoring of synchronization processes and provide audit trails of provisioning issues.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; IAM Identity Center is available at no additional cost in all &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/sso.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where it is supported. To learn more, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/singlesignon/latest/userguide/what-is.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS IAM Identity Center User Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-iam-identity-center</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-iam-identity-center-error-messages-cloudtrail-logging-provisioning-issues</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">812001e93889b3c7f3551812704293b294cc1e0d</guid>
			<title>AWS Elemental MediaTailor now supports log delivery to additional destinations</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Elemental MediaTailor now supports delivering logs to Amazon S3 and Amazon Data Firehose, in addition to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Additionally, customers now receive 50 KB of MediaTailor logs per ad inserted (50,000 KB per 1,000 ads inserted) for free when delivering to supported destinations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers delivering MediaTailor logs to CloudWatch logs benefit from advanced log analytics features such as Live Tailing, Anomaly Detection, and Logs Insights as well as metrics and dashboards to monitor ad monetization. Delivery to S3 or Firehose enables offline analysis and real-time streaming to other AWS services and third-party tools.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Usage over the free 50 KB per ad insert will be charged as per MediaTailor logs pricing. For details, please refer to the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/mediatailor/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing&lt;/a&gt; section of the MediaTailor product page.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Visit the AWS region table for a full list of &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where AWS Elemental MediaTailor is available. To learn more about MediaTailor, please visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/mediatailor/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/media-services,general:products/aws-elemental-mediatailor,general:products/amazon-cloudwatch</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-elemental-mediatailor-s3-firehose-logging-destinations-lower-cost</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">ae149492a9f0a46d0c0d5837605706329be1c81b</guid>
			<title>Amazon RDS for Oracle now supports January 2025 Release Update</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/rds/oracle/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS) for Oracle&lt;/a&gt; now supports the January 2025 Release Update (RU) for Oracle Database versions 19c and 21c.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about Oracle RUs supported on Amazon RDS for each engine version, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/OracleReleaseNotes/Welcome.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS for Oracle Release notes&lt;/a&gt;. If the auto minor version upgrade (AmVU) option is enabled, your DB instance is upgraded to the latest quarterly RU six to eight weeks after it is made available by Amazon RDS for Oracle in your AWS Region. These upgrades will happen during the maintenance window. To learn more, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/UserGuide/USER_UpgradeDBInstance.Maintenance.html#AdjustingTheMaintenanceWindow" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon RDS maintenance window documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For more information about the AWS Regions where Amazon RDS for Oracle is available, see the &lt;a href="http://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region&lt;/a&gt; table.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category/>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-rds-oracle-january-2025-release-update</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">83847e6acd5f2aac23199da037fe773bf3dfce48</guid>
			<title>Amazon MSK expands Express Brokers to 10 more AWS Regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon MSK has added support for Express brokers in all AWS Regions where Amazon MSK offers Graviton3 based M7g instances. You can now benefit from Amazon MSK Express brokers in ten additional AWS Regions: Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Europe (Paris), South America (Sao Paulo), Asia Pacific (Hyderabad), Asia Pacific (Seoul), Asia Pacific (Malaysia), Europe (London), Canada (Central), Europe (Spain), and Middle East (Bahrain).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Express brokers are a new broker type for Amazon MSK Provisioned designed to deliver up to 3x more throughput per broker, scale up to 20x faster, and reduce recovery time by 90% as compared to standard Apache Kafka brokers. Express brokers come pre-configured with Kafka best practices by default, support all Kafka APIs, and provide the same low-latency performance that Amazon MSK customers expect, so they can continue using existing client applications without any changes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can now create an MSK cluster with Express brokers in these AWS Regions from the Amazon MSK &lt;a href="https://us-east-2.signin.aws.amazon.com/oauth?client_id=arn%3Aaws%3Asignin%3A%3A%3Aconsole%2Fcanvas&amp;amp;code_challenge=Rx9g3IIBch8VAmdpe2UX_lsWypVnS0XbubpHyQf1ncU&amp;amp;code_challenge_method=SHA-256&amp;amp;response_type=code&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fconsole.aws.amazon.com%2Fconsole%2Fhome%3FhashArgs%3D%2523%26isauthcode%3Dtrue%26nc2%3Dh_ct%26src%3Dheader-signin%26state%3DhashArgsFromTB_us-east-2_9a482948c806810f" target="_blank"&gt;console&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more, check out this &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-express-brokers-for-amazon-msk-to-deliver-high-throughput-and-faster-scaling-for-your-kafka-clusters/" target="_blank"&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-msk,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-msk-express-brokers-10-regions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">a6b3aa7ef2e95b92f43412a54aefa0d49e36a80e</guid>
			<title>AWS AppSync releases CDK L2 constructs to simplify creating WebSocket APIs</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS AppSync Events allows developers to create serverless WebSocket APIs that can broadcast real-time data to millions of subscribers without managing infrastructure or connection state. Developers simply create their API, and publish events without having the worry about scale and handling fan-out. Today, AWS AppSync announces the release of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) L2 constructs for AWS AppSync Events, enabling developers to programmatically create and manage Event APIs and channel namespaces using infrastructure as code. These new constructs simplify the process of creating Event APIs and managing access controls, reducing the complexity of integrating real-time capabilities into applications.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The new L2 constructs provide a higher-level abstraction that makes it easier for developers to define AppSync Event APIs and their associated channel namespaces using familiar programming languages. Developers can now easily grant access to specific channel namespaces to AWS resources such as AWS Lambda functions, streamlining the integration between services. This eliminates the need to manually configure complex IAM permissions and reduces the potential for security misconfigurations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; These CDK L2 constructs are available in all AWS Regions where AWS AppSync is available. To get started with the new AWS AppSync Events CDK L2 constructs, visit the AWS CDK API Reference &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cdk/api/v2/docs/aws-cdk-lib.aws_appsync-readme.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/mobile-services,general:products/aws-appsync</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-appsync-cdk-l2-simplify-websocket-apis/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f25627d9d31e437828e7988be5ff605f7898ee5f</guid>
			<title>Amazon GuardDuty Malware Protection for S3 announces price reduction</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/gdu-malware-protection-s3.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon GuardDuty Malware Protection for Amazon S3&lt;/a&gt; provides a fully-managed offering to scan new object uploads to S3 bucket for malware. Starting February 1, 2025, we are lowering the price for the data scanned dimension by 85%. Over the past few months we have made improvements to our scanning infrastructure and data processing efficiencies, enabling us to reduce the price as part of our commitment to pass savings back to customers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; GuardDuty Malware Protection for S3 is priced based on two dimensions: the number of objects evaluated and the amount of data scanned. We are lowering the price for the data scanned dimension, for example in US East (N. Virginia) from $0.60 to $0.09 per GB. The price for objects evaluated remains unchanged. With this price reduction, you will be more capable of building secure and cost-effective data pipelines on Amazon S3 for applications with untrusted uploads across the enterprise.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The price reduction applies automatically to all AWS Regions where GuardDuty Malware Protection for S3 is available, requiring no action from customers. For additional information visit Amazon GuardDuty &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/guardduty/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt; pricing&lt;/a&gt; page. To receive programmatic updates on new GuardDuty features and threat detections, subscribe to the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/guardduty_sns.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon GuardDuty AWS Simple Notification Service (SNS) topic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/amazon-guardduty</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-guardduty-malware-protection-s3-price-reduction/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6193ea42d00667bc79fab26db9483880873288c1</guid>
			<title>Amazon Keyspaces is now available in Africa (Cape Town) Region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/keyspaces/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Keyspaces (for Apache Cassandra)&lt;/a&gt;, a scalable, highly available, and fully managed Cassandra-compatible database service, is now available in the Africa (Cape Town) Region.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With Amazon Keyspaces, you can run your Cassandra workloads on AWS using the same Cassandra application code and developer tools that you use today. The service is completely serverless, eliminating the need to provision, patch, or manage servers, or handle software installation and maintenance. You pay only for the resources you use, and tables automatically scale up and down based on application traffic. Amazon Keyspaces supports applications serving thousands of requests per second with virtually unlimited throughput and storage. The service includes built-in security features with encryption by default and continuous data backup capabilities through point-in-time recovery.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For pricing information in the Africa (Cape Town) Region, visit Amazon &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/keyspaces/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Keyspaces (for Apache Cassandra) pricing&lt;/a&gt;. To see the complete list of AWS Regions where Amazon Keyspaces is available, check &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regional Services&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To begin using Amazon Keyspaces in the Africa (Cape Town) Region, refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/keyspaces/latest/devguide/getting-started.html" target="_blank"&gt;Getting Started with Amazon Keyspaces (for Apache Cassandra)&lt;/a&gt; in the Amazon Keyspaces Developer Guide.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-keyspaces,marketing:marchitecture/databases</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-keyspaces-africa-cape-town-region</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">b1883aa7c8fb9e047ba7a2a6916f641001cba287</guid>
			<title>AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio Code now supports Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio Code (VSCode) now includes Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility). This integration allows customers to use VS Code to view, create and manage Amazon DocumentDB resources.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;To get started, you can download the &lt;a href="https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=AmazonWebServices.aws-toolkit-vscode" target="_blank"&gt;latest AWS-Toolkit extension&lt;/a&gt; from VSCode marketplace or update your AWS-Toolkit extension if you already have it installed in your VSCode environment. Then you can configure the extension with credentials for your AWS account and connect to AWS explorer in VSCode. Once connected, you can interact with the DocumentDB menu item to create DocumentDB clusters or manage your existing DocumentDB clusters.&lt;br&gt; To learn more, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/toolkit-for-vscode/latest/userguide/docdb.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon DocumentDB support in VSCode&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon DocumentDB is a fully managed, native JSON database that makes it simple and cost-effective to operate critical document workloads at virtually any scale without managing infrastructure. To learn more about Amazon DocumentDB, please visit the Amazon DocumentDB &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/documentdb/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/documentdb/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/documentdb/latest/developerguide/what-is.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,general:products/aws-toolkit-for-visual-studio</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-toolkit-visual-studio-code-documentdb-mongodb/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">43ae9a0e1f81e98144465ca8b023745d37878dc0</guid>
			<title>AWS Verified Access launches Zero Trust access to resources over non-HTTP(S) protocols</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS announces the general availability of AWS Verified Access’ support for secure access to resources that connect over protocols such as TCP, SSH, and RDP. With this launch, you can use Verified Access to provide secure VPN-less access to all your corporate applications and resources using &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/security/zero-trust/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS zero trust principles&lt;/a&gt;. This feature eliminates the need to manage separate access, and connectivity solutions for non-HTTP(S) resources on AWS and simplifies security operations.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Verified Access allows admins to set access policies based on user identity and device posture. It evaluates access for new connections and continuously monitors active connections, terminating connections when security requirements specified in the access policies aren't met. Now you can extend your existing Verified Access policies to enable secure access to non-HTTP(S) applications and resources such as databases, and SAP and git-repositories running on EC2 instances. For example, you can centrally define access policies granting prod database access only to authenticated database administrators using compliant, managed devices. This simplifies your security operations by allowing you to centrally create, group, and manage access policies for all applications and resources with similar security requirements from a single interface.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is generally available in 18 AWS regions: US East (Ohio), US East (Northern Virginia), US West (N California), US West (Oregon), Canada (Central), Asia Pacific (Sydney), Asia Pacific (Jakarta), Asia Pacific (Tokyo), Asia Pacific (Mumbai), Asia Pacific (Singapore), Asia Pacific (Sydney), Europe (Ireland), Europe (London), Europe (Frankfurt), Europe (Milan), Europe (Stockholm), South America (São Paulo), and Israel (Tel Aviv).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/verified-access/" target="_blank"&gt;product page&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/verified-access/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/verified-access/latest/ug/getting-started.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-verified-access</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-verified-access-zero-trust-resources-non-https-protocols/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2a25bcfa638627ee1bd3abc32a3a97d4392e14dd</guid>
			<title>Reshape your AWS CloudFormation stacks seamlessly with stack refactoring</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CloudFormation introduces a new capability called stack refactoring that makes it easy to reorganize cloud resources across your CloudFormation stacks. Stack refactoring enables you to move resources from one stack to another, split monolithic stacks into smaller components, and rename the logical name of resources within a stack. This enables you to adapt your stacks to meet architectural patterns, operational needs, or business requirements.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; As your workloads scale and requirements evolve, re-architecting resources into a new stack structure can become necessary. For example, you may need to split a monolithic stack for easier resource lifecycle management or rename resource logical IDs to align with new naming conventions. Previously, refactoring a stack required multiple manual steps, such as updating templates to retain targeted resources, removing them from current stacks, and then importing them into new stacks. Stack refactoring improves the speed and safety of this process. To refactor a stack, you first provide the CloudFormation templates that reflect the desired stack structure. Then, you generate a preview of the refactor operation, allowing you to confirm that the refactoring changes align with your requirements. If the planned changes meet your expectations, you can execute the refactor operation through an atomic workflow. This new capability enables seamless and continuous adaptation to evolving architectural patterns.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Stack refactor is available in all AWS Regions where CloudFormation is supported. To get started, update your CloudFormation templates to reflect the desired stack structure, then use the AWS CLI or SDK to perform the refactor operation. Visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-aws-cloudformation-stack-refactoring/" target="_blank"&gt;user guide&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about this feature.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-cloudformation,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/reshape-aws-cloudformation-stack-refactoring/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">bcc197a763be899829eca065872f50f75fa3c84b</guid>
			<title>Amazon Q Developer introduces a new, simplified setup experience for Pro tier subscriptions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we are excited to announce a new onboarding experience that makes it easy to set up and manage Amazon Q Developer Pro tier subscriptions. The workflow on Amazon Q console has been redesigned to provide a friendlier 2-step setup for users or teams that are looking to try out Amazon Q Developer in their Integrated Development Environment (IDE).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS account administrators can create subscriptions using the Amazon Q console for their standalone or AWS Organizations member accounts using a guided setup to create local users and configure Amazon Q Developer managed applications. Once the setup is complete, subscribed users will receive details on setting up credentials to start using Amazon Q Developer. After installation of the Amazon Q Developer plugin in their preferred IDE, users can leverage context-aware code recommendations and enhanced development capabilities to accelerate their software development. Administrators in the Organizations management accounts will continue to maintain their existing IAM Identity Center capabilities to manage workforce access to Amazon Q Developer.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about the new getting started experience, visit &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amazonq/latest/qdeveloper-ug/q-pro-tier-setting-up-access.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Q Developer User Guide&lt;/a&gt;. To get started with Amazon Q Developer, visit the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/amazonq/home" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Console&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/developer-tools,general:products/amazon-q</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-q-developer-experience-pro-tier-subscriptions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">7527991603572c0c1d4f24d722c051de43e98c4e</guid>
			<title>Cost Optimization Hub supports more EC2 Auto Scaling group recommendations</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Cost Optimization Hub now supports idle EC2 Auto Scaling group recommendations and rightsizing recommendations for EC2 Auto Scaling groups with scaling policies and multiple instance types. It also allows you to easily filter and aggregate EC2 Auto Scaling group cost optimization opportunities separately from standalone EC2 instances,&amp;nbsp;making it easier to identify EC2 Auto Scaling groups with the highest cost-saving opportunities.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;With this launch, you can view, consolidate, and prioritize cost optimization opportunities for EC2 Auto Scaling groups across your organization’s member accounts and AWS Regions through a single dashboard. Cost Optimization Hub helps you quantify estimated savings from these recommendations, taking into account your specific discounts, such as Reserved Instances and Savings Plans, enabling you to easily compare and prioritize recommendations.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;The new EC2 Auto Scaling group experience and recommendations are available in &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/aws-cost-management/cost-optimization-hub/" target="_blank"&gt;Cost Optimization Hub&lt;/a&gt; across all &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt; where Cost Optimization Hub and AWS Organizations are supported.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/compute,general:products/amazon-ec2-auto-scaling,general:products/cloud-financial-management</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/cost-optimization-hub-ec2-auto-scaling-group-recommendations/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">cfa815f7f2d7006ac51f72c819708217ed54d67e</guid>
			<title>Amazon Personalize now supports Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Personalize introduces dual stack support for the Personalize API endpoints, enabling you to connect using Internet Protocol Version 6 (IPv6), Internet Protocol Version 4 (IPv4), or dual stack clients. Dual stack support is also available when you privately access the Personalize API endpoint from your Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) using AWS PrivateLink.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The urgency to transition to Internet Protocol version 6 (IPv6) is driven by the continued growth of internet, which is exhausting available Internet Protocol version 4 (IPv4) addresses. With simultaneous support for both IPv4 and IPv6 clients on Personalize endpoints, you are able to gradually transition from IPv4 to IPv6 based systems and applications, without needing to switch all over at once. This enables you to help meet IPv6 compliance requirements and removes the need for expensive networking equipment to handle the address translation between IPv4 and IPv6.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Support for IPv6 on Amazon Personalize in &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/personalize.html" target="_blank"&gt;all supported regions&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more on best practices for configuring IPv6, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/latest/ipv6-on-aws/internet-protocol-version-6.html" target="_blank"&gt;whitepaper&lt;/a&gt; on IPv6 in AWS.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-personalize,general:products/amazon-machine-learning,marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-personalize-supports-ipv6/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">f80e998b7ac16a5fe0ed00d72ec82b2034f8ebbf</guid>
			<title>Amazon ECS Service Connect is now available in the AWS GovCloud (US-West) and AWS GovCloud (US-East) Regions</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ecs/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Elastic Container Service &lt;/a&gt;(Amazon ECS) launches its networking capability called ECS Service Connect in the AWS GovCloud (US-West) and AWS GovCloud (US-East) Regions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon ECS is a fully managed container orchestration service that makes it easier for you to deploy, manage, and scale containerized applications. With ECS Service Connect, customers can easily configure service discovery, connectivity, traffic observability, and encryption for services running in Amazon ECS. This enables more efficient application development by allowing you to focus on writing application code instead of managing complex networking infrastructure&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more about how to get started with Amazon ECS Service Connect and how it works, see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonECS/latest/developerguide/service-connect.html" target="_blank"&gt;our documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ecs,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/containers</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ecs-service-connect-aws-govcloud-regions</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6ad4aa79401b45e6fbbe064b71b139873d0ef494</guid>
			<title>Amazon DocumentDB now offers one-click connectivity with CloudShell</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can connect to your Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility) clusters with a single click through AWS CloudShell directly from the AWS Management Console. This new feature allows our customers to easily connect to their DocumentDB clusters directly from their browser, without requiring any local setup.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; One-click connectivity with Cloudshell automatically configures VPCs, security groups, and MongoDB shell installation, eliminating the need for manual tasks like setting up security groups and ingress/egress rules. This streamlines the process for database administrators and developers, enabling them to connect quickly to their DocumentDB cluster to preview data or execute adhoc queries.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all AWS Regions where both Amazon DocumentDB and AWS CloudShell services are supported. For more information about region availability, see the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region&lt;/a&gt; table. To get started, follow &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/documentdb/latest/developerguide/get-started-guide.html" target="_blank"&gt;Get started with Amazon DocumentDB&lt;/a&gt; to create an Amazon DocumentDB cluster, then click the "Connect to cluster" button to connect via CloudShell.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-documentdb</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-documentdb-one-click-connectivity-cloudshell</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">183cdcdce793ec8ffe45fe8cedacfe3cbac1f580</guid>
			<title>Amazon SageMaker AI is now available in Asia Pacific (Malaysia)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, you can build, train, and deploy machine learning (ML) models in Asia Pacific (Malaysia).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon SageMaker AI is a fully managed platform that provides every developer and data scientist with the ability to build, train, and deploy machine learning (ML) models quickly. SageMaker AI removes the heavy lifting from each step of the machine learning process to make it easier to develop high quality models.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more and get started, see SageMaker AI &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/sagemaker/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/sagemaker/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-sagemaker</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-sagemaker-ai-asia-pacific-malaysia</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">27941661336464c03f81f72618cf243c1de9724b</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 M6in and M6idn instances are now available in Europe (Zurich)</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) M6in and M6idn instances are available in AWS Europe (Zurich) region. These sixth-generation network optimized instances, powered by 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors and built on the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/nitro/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Nitro System&lt;/a&gt;, deliver up to 200Gbps network bandwidth, for 2x more network bandwidth over comparable fifth-generation instances. Customers can use M6in and M6idn instances to scale their performance and throughput of network-intensive workloads such as high-performance file systems, distributed web scale in-memory caches, caching fleets, real-time big data analytics, and Telco applications such as 5G User Plane Function.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; M6in and M6idn instances are available in 10 different instance sizes including metal, offering up to 128 vCPUs and 512 GiB of memory. They deliver up to 100Gbps of &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ebs/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS)&lt;/a&gt; bandwidth, and up to 400K IOPS. M6in and M6idn instances offer &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/hpc/efa/" target="_blank"&gt;Elastic Fabric Adapter (EFA)&lt;/a&gt; networking support on 32xlarge and metal sizes. M6idn instances offer up to 7.6 TB of high-speed, low-latency instance storage.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this regional expansion, M6in and M6idn instances are available in the following AWS Regions: US East (Ohio, N. Virginia), US West (N. California, Oregon), Europe (Ireland, Frankfurt, Spain, Stockholm, Zurich), Asia Pacific (Mumbai, Singapore, Tokyo, Sydney), Canada (Central), and AWS GovCloud (US-West). Customers can purchase the new instances through Savings Plans, On-Demand, and Spot instances. To learn more, see &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/m6i/" target="_blank"&gt;M6in and M6idn instances page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-m6in-m6idn-instances-europe-zurich</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">404314ec017613430a4fbff7b485af84460050bf</guid>
			<title>Amazon Q Business introduces orchestration for user query management</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Q Business, the generative AI-powered assistant for finding information, gaining insight, and taking action at work, introduced an intelligent orchestration feature that simplifies conversational experience by understanding user queries, and automatically directing the queries to the right data sources and plugins to generate relevant responses.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Earlier, users would need to manually switch between different work applications to complete their tasks and gain insights from data sources. Enabling orchestration simplifies the user conversational experience by automatically directing user queries to indexed enterprise data sources and plugins, eliminating the need for manual selection. Orchestration works with retrieval augmented generative (RAG) data for enterprise-specific knowledge, and with both built-in and custom plugins, allowing users to interact with popular business tools like Jira, Salesforce, ServiceNow, Smartsheet, and PagerDuty - all through a single conversation in Amazon Q Business.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The new orchestration feature is available in all AWS Regions where Amazon Q Business is available. To get started with the feature, customers can access the setting directly from the Amazon Q Business console. To learn more, please visit &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amazonq/latest/qbusiness-ug/guardrails-global-controls.html#guardrails-global-orchestration" target="_blank"&gt;Using global controls in Amazon Q Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; To learn more about Amazon Q Business plugins and how they can enhance your organization's productivity, visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/q/business/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Q Business webpage&lt;/a&gt; and explore the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/amazonq/latest/qbusiness-ug/plugins.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon Q Business plugin documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/artificial-intelligence,general:products/amazon-q,marketing:marchitecture/application-services,marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-q-business-orchestration-user-query-management</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e401fa73f6bab68e5b57ade3b195dbd51e2575ed</guid>
			<title>Announcing the general availability of Amazon EC2 F2.6xlarge, a new F2 instance size</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS is announcing the general availability of a new smaller size of Amazon EC2 F2 instances, F2.6xlarge. Amazon EC2 F2 instances are the second-generation of FPGA-powered instances, purpose built for developing and deploying reconfigurable hardware in the cloud. The new F2.6xlarge instance size has 1 FPGA, compared to the currently available F2 sizes with 4 and 8 FPGAs.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Amazon EC2 F2 instances are ideal for FPGA-accelerated solutions in genomics, multimedia processing, big data, network acceleration, and more. AWS customers can use the new instance size, F2.6xlarge, for applications that are more cost-efficient or performant when running on a single FPGA. F2.6xlarge also provides a lower cost entry point to using F2 instances.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; F2 instances are the first to feature an FPGA with 16 GB of high bandwidth memory (HBM). The new F2.6xlarge size features a 3rd generation AMD EPYC processor with 24 vCPUs, 256 GB of system memory, 950 GB of NVMe SSD local storage, and 12.5 Gbps of network bandwidth.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The F2.6xlarge size is now available in the US East (N. Virginia), Europe (London), and US West (Oregon) &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt;. To learn more, please visit the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/f2/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon EC2 F2 Instances page.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-f2-6xlarge-new-f2-instance-size/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">9e91e5b810727f6bf91cd92b557531ee80d490eb</guid>
			<title>AWS IAM announces support for encrypted SAML assertions </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) announced support for encrypted SAML assertions. SAML is an open standard that many identity providers (IdPs) use for federated single sign-on (SSO), enabling users or applications in your company to log into the AWS Management Console or call AWS API operations. You can now configure your identity provider to encrypt the SAML assertions that it sends to IAM. This ensures that your assertions are encrypted when passed through intermediaries (for example, the end user’s web browser).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; You can use the AWS IAM console, APIs, or CLI to configure SAML encryption for your identity providers that support encryption. Please refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_providers_create_saml.html" target="_blank"&gt;IAM&lt;/a&gt; and your identity provider’s product documentation for detailed configuration steps.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all AWS commercial and AWS GovCloud (US) Regions. To learn more, please refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html" target="_blank"&gt;IAM documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-iam,general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-iam-encrypted-saml-assertions/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">dfcf9a0d66d0d8531062c61211886851673cdbd4</guid>
			<title>AWS Wickr now provides a dedicated space to organize and access files</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Wickr is excited to announce the launch of "Wickr Files" a dedicated space that allows you to access and manage files in conversations. Moderators of Wickr rooms and users in self-moderated group conversations can now upload and organize files in folders. Users can toggle between “Messages” and “Files” tabs to access relevant content and streamline collaboration.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS Wickr is a security-first messaging and collaboration service with features designed to help keep your internal and external communications secure, private, and compliant. AWS Wickr protects one-to-one and group messaging, voice and video calling, file sharing, screen sharing, and location sharing with end-to-end encryption. Customers have full administrative control over data, which includes addressing information governance polices, configuring ephemeral messaging options, and deleting credentials for lost or stolen devices. You can log both internal and external conversations in an AWS Wickr network to a private data store that you manage, for data retention and auditing purposes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; AWS Wickr is available in commercial AWS Regions that include US East (N. Virginia), AWS Canada (Central), AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia, Singapore, Sydney, and Tokyo), and AWS Europe (London, Frankfurt, Stockholm, and Zurich). It is also available in AWS GovCloud (US-West) as Department of Defense Impact Level 5 (DoD IL5)-authorized AWS WickrGov.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more and get started, see the following resources:&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;ul&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/wickr/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Wickr product detail page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/wickr/latest/userguide/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Wickr user guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
 &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/wickr/latest/adminguide/getting-started.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Wickr administration guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,marketing:marchitecture/security-identity-and-compliance,general:products/aws-wickr,marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-wickr-dedicated-space-organize-access-files</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">9551c9d63f761514407129ffbaf7109671b804af</guid>
			<title>Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2 is now available in Asia Pacific (Malaysia) region</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon Redshift announces the general availability of Query Editor V2 with Amazon Redshift in the Asia Pacific (Malaysia) region. Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2 makes data in your Amazon Redshift data warehouse and data lake more accessible with a web-based tool for SQL users such as data analysts, data scientists, and database developers. With Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2, users can explore, analyze, and collaborate on data. It reduces the operational costs of managing query tools by providing a web-based application that allows you to focus on exploring your data without managing your infrastructure.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; The Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2 is a separate web-based SQL client application that you use to author and run queries on your Amazon Redshift data warehouse. You can use it to edit and run queries, visualize results, and share your work with your team. With Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2, you can create databases, schemas, tables, and user-defined functions (UDFs). In a tree-view panel, for each of your databases, you can view its schemas. For each schema, you can view its tables, views, UDFs, and stored procedures. The Amazon Redshift Query Editor V2 comes with sample data and notebooks available for you to be loaded into a sample database and corresponding schema. You can use it to load data into a database in an Amazon Redshift cluster or workgroup.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; To learn more, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/query-editor-v2.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqiAsQOrwTs" target="_blank"&gt;demo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/analytics,marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/amazon-redshift</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-redshift-query-editor-v2-malaysia-region/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">09a9287ed65d5a6857a6165db4419a7e5dade0ed</guid>
			<title>AWS Step Functions now supports 100,000 state machines and activities per AWS account</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Step Functions has increased the default quota for the maximum number of registered state machines and activities from 10,000 to 100,000. This tenfold increase enables customers to create and manage significantly more workflows within a single AWS account, providing greater scalability and flexibility.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/step-functions/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Step Functions&lt;/a&gt; is a visual workflow service capable of orchestrating over 14,000+ API actions from over 220 AWS services to build distributed applications and orchestrate data processing workloads. With this quota increase, customers can now create up to 100,000 state machines and activities, unblocking use cases that require a large number of workflows such as applications that dynamically create new workflows. This new quota is automatically applied to all AWS accounts and requires no action on your part.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This quota increase is available in all AWS Regions where Step Functions is available. To learn more, see the &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/step-functions/latest/dg/service-quotas.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Step Functions Developer Guide.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/aws-govcloud-us,general:products/aws-step-functions,marketing:marchitecture/application-services</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/aws-step-functions-100-000-state-machines-activities-account/</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">e14acbc7c3e97ecadf4fc26d1eb06a9c9660fca3</guid>
			<title>Announcing the general availability of AWS Database Migration Service Serverless support for files with an S3 source endpoint</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;AWS Database Migration Service Serverless (AWS DMSS) now supports files on S3 source endpoints. Using AWS DMSS, you can now migrate data in CSV or parquet format from S3 to any supported AWS DMSS target endpoint. AWS DMSS supports both full load and Change Data Capture (CDC) migration modes for CSV and Parquet files with S3 source endpoints using AWS DMS console, AWS CLI, or AWS SDKs in &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/dms/latest/userguide/CHAP_ReplicationInstance.html" target="_blank"&gt;all regions where DMSS is available.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For information about AWS DMS S3 source endpoints see &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/dms/latest/userguide/CHAP_Source.S3.html" target="_blank"&gt;DMS S3&lt;/a&gt;. Visit &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/dms/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS DMS&lt;/a&gt; to get started.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; For AWS DMS regional availability, please refer to the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Region Table&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/databases,general:products/aws-database-migration-service,general:products/amazon-s3</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/general-availability-aws-database-migration-service-serverless-files-s3-source-endpoint</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6b6d43e4204ea19d325bd80dedba4da2f67cf6d0</guid>
			<title>Amazon Connect Contact Lens can now automatically email agents about completed performance evaluations</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Contact Lens now enables businesses to send automatic email notifications to agents when their contacts are evaluated, so they can review the evaluations and improve their performance. Managers can create rules to send emails based on specific evaluation criteria. For example, you can set up automatic notifications for agents who receive evaluation scores below 50%, ensuring prompt attention to performance opportunities. Managers can also personalize email content based on performance levels — whether recognizing top performers or providing constructive guidance for improvement areas.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This feature is available in all regions where Contact Lens performance evaluations are already available. To learn more, please visit our &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/connect/latest/adminguide/contact-lens-rules-email.html" target="_blank"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/contact-lens/" target="_blank"&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt;. For information about Contact Lens pricing, please visit our &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/connect/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;pricing page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-connect,marketing:marchitecture/business-productivity</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-connect-contact-lens-automatically-email-agents-completed-performance-evaluations</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">6ab9c99ccc96fcecdf4c809159db08d32b4188de</guid>
			<title>Amazon CloudWatch and OpenSearch Service expand region support for integrated analytics experience</title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Amazon CloudWatch and OpenSearch Service integrated analytics experience is now available in 2 additional commercial regions: Asia Pacific (Hong Kong) and Europe (Stockholm).&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this integration, CloudWatch Logs customers have two more query languages for log analytics, in addition to CloudWatch Logs Insights QL. Customers can use SQL to analyze data, correlate logs using JOIN, sub-queries, and use SQL functions, namely, JSON, mathematical, datetime, and string functions for intuitive log analytics. They can also use the OpenSearch PPL to filter, aggregate and analyze their data. With a few clicks, CloudWatch Logs customers can create OpenSearch dashboards for VPC, WAF, and CloudTrail logs to monitor, analyze, and troubleshoot using visualizations derived from the logs. OpenSearch customers no longer have to copy logs from CloudWatch for analysis, or create ETL pipelines. Now, they can use OpenSearch Discover to analyze CloudWatch logs in-place, and build indexes and dashboards on CloudWatch Logs.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; With this launch the integrated experience is now generally available in Asia Pacific (Hong Kong) and Europe (Stockholm) along with regions where &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/latest/developerguide/direct-query-s3.html#direct-query-cloudwatch-logs-regions-table" target="_blank"&gt;OpenSearch Service direct query&lt;/a&gt; is available. Please read pricing and free tier details on &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cloudwatch/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon CloudWatch Pricing&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/pricing/" target="_blank"&gt;OpenSearch Service Pricing&lt;/a&gt;. To get started, please refer to &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/logs//CloudWatchLogs-OpenSearch-Dashboards.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon CloudWatch Logs vended dashboard&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/opensearch-service/latest/developerguide/direct-query-s3.html" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon OpenSearch Service Developer Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>marketing:marchitecture/management-and-governance,general:products/amazon-cloudwatch,marketing:marchitecture/storage,general:products/amazon-opensearch-service,marketing:marchitecture/analytics</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-cloudwatch-opensearch-service-expand-region-integrated-analytics-experience</link>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">d9970669882914b22c091c241d6e18e48784a5fd</guid>
			<title>Amazon EC2 C6in instances are now available in Asia Pacific (Malaysia) </title>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Starting today, Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) C6in instances are available in AWS Region Asia Pacific (Malaysia). These sixth-generation network optimized instances, powered by 3rd Generation Intel Xeon Scalable processors and built on the &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/nitro/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Nitro System&lt;/a&gt;, deliver up to 200Gbps network bandwidth, for 2x more network bandwidth over comparable fifth-generation instances.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Customers can use C6in instances to scale the performance of applications such as network virtual appliances (firewalls, virtual routers, load balancers), Telco 5G User Plane Function (UPF), data analytics, high performance computing (HPC), and CPU based AI/ML workloads. C6in instances are available in 10 different sizes with up to 128 vCPUs, including bare metal size. Amazon EC2 sixth-generation x86-based network optimized EC2 instances deliver up to 100Gbps of Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) bandwidth, and up to 400K IOPS. C6in instances offer Elastic Fabric Adapter (EFA) networking support on 32xlarge and metal sizes.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; C6in instances are available in these &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regional-product-services/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Regions&lt;/a&gt;: US East (Ohio, N. Virginia), US West (N. California, Oregon), Europe (Frankfurt, Ireland, London, Milan, Paris, Spain, Stockholm, Zurich), Middle East (Bahrain, UAE), Israel (Tel Aviv), Asia Pacific (Hong Kong, Hyderabad, Jakarta, Malaysia, Melbourne, Mumbai, Seoul, Singapore, Sydney, Tokyo), Africa (Cape Town), South America (São Paulo), Canada (Central), and AWS GovCloud (US-West, US-East). To learn more, see the Amazon EC2 &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/c6i/" target="_blank"&gt;C6in&lt;/a&gt; instances. To get started, see the &lt;a href="https://console.aws.amazon.com/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Management Console&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/cli/" target="_blank"&gt;AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSJavaScriptSDK/latest/AWS/EC2.html" target="_blank"&gt;AWS SDKs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<category>general:products/amazon-ec2,marketing:marchitecture/compute</category>
			<author>aws@amazon.com</author>
			<link>https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2025/02/amazon-ec2-c6in-instances-asia-pacific-malaysia</link>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
